字幕來源：2017年4K修復版藍光碟
字幕風格：台灣三區Mandarin-R3
轉換製作：非傲慢即偏見@SubHD
主演：艾爾帕西諾、勞勃狄尼洛
片名：烈 火 悍 將
主演：方基墨
主演：湯姆賽斯摩
主演：黛安薇諾拉
主演：艾美步娜曼
主演：丹尼斯海斯伯特
主演：艾希莉賈德
主演：米凱帝威廉森
主演：韋斯史塔帝
主演：泰德李凡
主演：威廉費區納
主演：娜塔莉波曼
主演：湯姆諾南
主演: 凱文凱吉、漢克阿薩瑞亞
主演：蘇珊泰勒、金史坦頓
主演：強沃特
是，你可以先把她留在走道上
Yeah, you can leave her in the hallway for now.
- 情況穩定 - 攜帶型X光機在哪？
- Stabilizing here. - Where's the portable x-ray?
（古德休救護車）
（洛杉磯消防局）
製片：麥克曼恩、亞特林森
編劇兼導演：麥克曼恩
支票、信用卡還是現金？
Check, charge or cash?
現金
Cash. And, uh...
發票寫土桑市傑克拆除公司
...make it out to Jack's Demolition, Tucson.
788元3毛
Seven eighty-eight thirty.
好
Okay.
（炸藥）
嘿
Hey.
要帶我去吃早餐嗎？
Taking me to breakfast?
不行，我得見博斯高
I can't, I'm meeting Bosko.
嘿，文森
Hey, Vincent.
- 我的髮夾呢？ - 親愛的，早安
- Mom, where are my barrettes? - Hi, sweetie.
- 我在廚房的桌上看到過 - 沒在那，我找過了
- I saw them on the kitchen table. - They're not there. I already checked.
- 要我煮咖啡嗎？ - 今天不用上學？
- Want me to make coffee? - No school today?
爸爸要帶我去看新大樓，然後去吃午餐
My dad's taking me to the new building and then to lunch.
去沙發墊子下找找看
Try under the cushions on the sofa.
他已經遲到了半個小時
He's already a half an hour late.
那混蛋會出現，還是像上次那樣爽約？
He gonna show? Or that son of a bitch gonna stand her up like last time?
- 我去煮咖啡 - 沒時間了
- I'll make coffee. - I'm out of time, babe.
媽，我的髮夾呢？不在沙發那裏
Mom, where are my barrettes? They're not in the couch.
戴藍色的那一個
Wear the blue ones.
我不想戴藍色的，顏色不配
I don't wanna wear the blue ones. They don't match.
- 浴室找過了沒有？ - 全都找過了
- Did you check in your bathroom? - I checked everywhere.
- 那你要我怎麼樣？ - 去找出來
- Well, what do you want me to do? - Find them.
- 媽，專心聽我說 - 好，親愛的，怎麼了？
- Mom, pay attention. - All right, sweetie, all right. What?
- 爸爸馬上就會來 - 他會···
- Daddy's gonna be here. - Okay, he's gonna...
我還沒準備好，我不能遲到
I'm not gonna be ready. I can't be late.
- 你不會遲到的 - 我會遲到的
- You won't be late. - No, I will be late.
如果我們一起找，你爸來到前會找到
Okay. Before Daddy comes, we can find them if we look together.
- 沒事的，寶貝 - 不
- It's all right, baby. It's all right. - No.
沒事的，沒事的
It's all right. It's all right.
我們一起找，我和你一起找
We'll find them together, you and me. We'll find them together.
放心，他來前我們會找到的，我保證
Just relax. He won't come before we find them. I promise you.
嘿，我要續杯
Hey. Give me another refill.
他現在要續杯
Now he wants a refill.
- 你叫什麼？ - 韋恩葛羅
- What's your name? - Waingro.
你是麥克？
You're Michael, huh?
你們常一起合作？
You guys always work together?
經常合作
All the time.
- 合作無間？ - 是的
- Real tight crew, huh? - Real tight.
如果這次順利，我會考慮再做
Yeah, if this works good, I'd consider going again, you know.
好，別再說話，滑頭
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
- 情況如何？ - 百分之百
- How's he doing? - A hundred percent.
分秒不差
Right on schedule.
他們在威尼斯大道右轉
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
- 我們距離你一英哩半 - 好
- We're a mile and a half from you. - Okay.
他們剛上快車道，離你300碼
Just crossed over the number-one lane, 300 yards from you now.
- 準備 - 準備好了
- Get set. - I am.
戴上
Put that on.
行動
Here we go.
（蓋齊裝甲快遞）
有劫案！我們遇劫
Two eleven! Two eleven! We're being held up!
- 裝甲車遇劫 - 已通知了警方
Two-eleven alarm. Armored car.
3分鐘
There's the call. Three minutes.
離開！
Clear!
只剩80秒！
Eighty seconds left!
退後，退後
Get back. Get back.
退後！
Get back!
滑頭，你看到他們耳朵流血了嗎？
Hey, Slick, you see that shit coming out of their ears?
他們聽不到的，冷靜下來
They can't fucking hear you. Cool it.
找到了
I got it.
到手了
Got it.
你要和我過不去
You had to fuck with me.
和我過不去？
You wanna fuck with me?
快點，搞什麼鬼？
Come on! What the fuck are you doing?
- 你幹了什麼好事？ - 我沒有選擇
- What did you do? - I had to, man.
- 他作勢要攻擊 - 走吧
- Guy was making a move. - Let's go.
你這蠢貨
Dumb motherfucker.
- 先生，請退後 - 我有聽到他們
- Step back, please, sir. - I heard them.
160萬
A million six.
每元分4毛，你可得64萬
Forty cents on the dollar, 640,000 to you.
這是15萬的預支
Here's a 150 front money.
其餘的兩三天後付
Get you the rest in two, three days.
那些是誰的？
Know who owned these?
「馬裏布股票及投資公司」
Malibu Equity and Investments.
羅傑凡贊，在開曼群島擁有銀行
Roger Van Zant. Owns banks in the Caymans.
負責替國外販毒得來的錢投資
Runs investment portfolios for offshore drug money. Stuff like that.
- 所以呢？ - 你偷了他的債券
- So? - So you ripped off his bearer bonds.
他有買保險
He's got insurance.
重點就是他可以拿到 百分之百的保險賠償
That's the point. He collects 100 percent from the insurance.
他是玩家 也許會以六折價向我們購回債券
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds back from us for 60 percent of their value.
多賺四成
And make 40 percent on top of the 100 percent.
如果能把債券賣回給他 你可以再得32萬
Sell it back to him instead of going to the street. That's an extra 320,000 to you.
試試吧
Try it on him.
- 科索來電說 - 什麼事？
- Kelso called. - About what?
他想找人參與買賣
A score he's putting out and wants you to look at.
我不需要，我自己有買賣
What do I need his score for? I got my own.
他說無法追查，而且價值超過千萬元
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
- 明早九點 - 你們發生了什麼事？
- 9 a.m. tomorrow. - What happened out there?
別問了
Don't ask.
找到救護車了嗎？
Find the ambulance?
- 在四條街外遭棄 - 在22街的費古洛街和花街中間
- Dumped it four blocks from here. - 22nd Street between Figueroa and Flower.
被縱了火，槍和衣服都燒成灰燼
They torched it. Burned everything. The guns, clothes, everything.
警方仍在現場調查···
Investigators are still working the scene...
他們在空中，拍下了最後幾秒
They were airborne. Taped the last few seconds...
警車相撞的黑白畫面
...of the black-and-whites doing demolition derby.
兩星期前在夫雷士諾被偷
Stolen out of Fresno two weeks ago.
黃色卡車是前天在惠蒂爾被偷
Yellow pickup truck out of whittier day before yesterday.
小隊長，你負責此案？ 還是由分局調查？
You taking this one, lieutenant, or does it stay in Division?
這看起來像一宗便利商店劫案嗎？
This look like gangbangers working the local 7-11 to you?
- 搶劫及兇案組接手調查 - 交給你們了
- Robbery-Homicide's taking it. Yeah. - All yours.
三名司機目擊事發 只看見戴面具的人，他們在遠處
We got three motorists. All they saw were men with masks. They were distant.
但那位裝有線電視的比較接近現場
Console TV man over there however, he was closer.
他有認出任何人嗎？
He ID anybody?
他躲起來，聽到大部分對話
Well, he was hiding. He heard it mostly.
好，那他們呢？
Okay. What about them?
那個有線電視的說這人開始亂罵
Right. Now, according to TV man, this guy started mouthing off.
- 真明智 - 是，有人叫其中一個守衛「滑頭」
- Smart. - Yeah, somebody called a guard "Slick".
- 滑頭？ - 是的
- Slick? - Yeah.
我認為此人想拿綁在足踝的槍
Now, this guy... I figure this guy went for that holdout piece, ankle holster, right?
從這裏
From here.
磅、磅、磅、磅、磅
Bang. Bang. Bang, bang, bang.
他側身倒下
To his side.
這人看來似乎是胸部中了兩槍
This guy here has got what appears to be a double-tap entry wound to the sternum.
從頭的傷勢，燒焦的骨頭看來 是近距離被殺
Tattooing around the head wound, scorched bone, close range.
應該是一槍斃命
Probably executed.
160萬的債券被盜，他們沒拿走現金
And it was a million six in bearer bonds, and they ignored the loose cash.
因為他們沒時間，他們有計時
Because they had no time, because they were on a clock.
這代表他們知道警方何時會到達
Which means they knew our response time to a 2-11...
聽警方廣播，把車截停、進入
...had our air, immobilized it, entered...
逃走，全在三分鐘內搞定
...escaped in under three minutes.
這是好地點，有很好的逃走路線
It's a good spot here. We got good escape routes.
- 在四分之一哩之內有兩條公路 - 交通監視器呢？
- Two freeways within a quarter of a mile. - Traffic video camera?
可能被破壞了，但還是查一下
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
你認出手法了嗎？
You recognize the M.O.?
手法就是他們很厲害
M.O. is that they're good.
當他們殺了兩個警衛
Once it escalated into a murder-one beef for all of them...
犯了一級謀殺罪後，便不再遲疑
...after they killed the first two guards, they didn't hesitate...
殺了第三名，因為··· 反正沒有差別
...popped guard number three because what difference does it make?
為何留活口？
Why leave a living witness?
在危機時刻，這些人亳不遲疑
Drop of a hat, these guys will rock 'n' roll.
錐孔裝藥
The shape charge.
顯示劫匪的技術是純熟的
The shape charge indicates that they are technically proficient.
純熟到他們能在運送途中出手
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
從最近幾宗大竊盜懸案開始查起
So let's start looking for recent high-line burglaries that have mystified us.
查聯邦調查局檔案有「滑頭」這綽號的
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI.
名單可能很長，但還是要查
You're gonna get the phone book. Do it anyway.
誰負責脫手債券？
Who's moving the bearer bonds?
查慣常收贓者 你和我查庫蘇馬諾和陶瑞納
Check the usual fences. You and I will check Cusamano and Torena.
我要你查高斯汀及阿法洛 和監識科緊密合作
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro. Hang in with Forensics.
向炸彈組查問用的是什麼炸藥
From the bomb squad, I want the explosive.
要是幸運是罕見的，可追查發售來源
If we're lucky, it's exotic. We can trace the sale.
你別亂摸那男人的口袋，瑞秋
Get your hand out of that man's pocket, Rachel.
喔，文森
Oh, Vince.
有誰要吃派嗎？
Want some pie?
我去上廁所
Gotta go to the john.
他作勢攻擊，我得先下手為強
Look, I had to get it on, man. He was making a move. I had to get it on.
他那份在車上，由我們先均分
Split's in the car. I took out of ours evenly...
把他的那份都給他
...to make up for his full end.
因為我想立即分贓並打發這雜種
Because I wanna pay off and get rid of this motherfucker right now.
好
Okay.
等等！
Hold it!
嘿
Hey.
- 其餘的錢呢？ - 我們遲到了
- Where's the rest? - We're late.
你打扮得這麼漂亮 我想在這裏和你做愛
Ooh, you look too good to go out. I could just jump you right here.
- 錢呢？ - 給組頭了
- Where is it? - Uh, squared the bookies, baby.
幾天後還會有錢，放心吧 我們真的遲到了
There's more in a couple days, so don't sweat it. We really are late.
得了吧，你肯定是說笑
Yeah, come on, you gotta be kidding me.
親愛的，為區區八千元
Honey, it ain't worth the risks you take for 8000.
值得冒這個險嗎？
Like in risk versus reward, baby.
走吧，拿你的外套
Let's go. Get your coat.
跟你說沒用，你心智尚未成熟
There is no point talking to you. All you are is a child growing older.
什麼意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
意思是我們不像其他成年人那樣在進步 過該過的生活
It means we're not making forward progress like real grown-up adults, living our lives.
因為我嫁給了一個不聽我說話的賭徒
I'm married to a gambling junkie who won't listen.
夏琳，快上車吧
Charlene, get in the fucking car.
我怎麼能夠這樣下去？
What am I doing in this rat-bastard situation?
你可以不用！你要我怎樣？ 你離開這裏時，把銀行存摺和車鑰匙
You're not! What do you want from me? Leave the bankbook and car keys...
留在廚房，我們到底要不要去 還是我一個人去？
...in the kitchen on your way out. Are we going, or am I going alone?
那些垃圾你可以留著 我會帶多明尼克走
You could keep that other crap but Dominick would go with me.
你休想···
Don't you even think about...
告訴我亞伯特陶瑞納回電話了
Yeah. Tell me Albert Torena called back.
- 亞伯特陶瑞納有打給文森嗎？ - 沒有
- Albert Torena call Vincent? - No.
沒有，報告出來了
No. Report came in.
炸藥是戴尼克斯 在拆屋時用的線性聚能炸藥
The explosive was Dynex, linear-shaped charge used in demolition.
只要駕照，就可在內華達 亞利桑那、新墨西哥州買到
You can pick it up with a driver's license in Nevada, Arizona, New Mexico.
- 太普通，難以追查來源，文森 - 太好了
- Too common to trace a sale, Vincent. - Oh, that's wonderful.
你沒事吧？
Are you all right?
怎麼了？你去了哪裏？
What happened? Where you been?
工作
Work.
蘿倫的父親有來嗎？
Lauren's dad show up?
沒打電話，沒出現，我們等你到十點半
Didn't call, didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
這人知道他女兒過得怎樣嗎？
Now, does this guy have any idea what's going on with his kid?
我不知道
I don't know.
該死的混蛋
Fucking jerk.
那她沒事吧？
Well, is she okay?
她整天在房間裏
She's been in her room all day.
所以她有事，我也不開心
So no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
我為我們做了晚餐，四個小時前
Uh, I made dinner for us, four hours ago. Um...
每次我設法替我們保持一貫的情緒 你就會退卻
Every time I try to maintain a consistent mood between us, you withdraw.
在威尼斯大道旁邊躺著三名死人 賈絲汀
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
對不起
I'm sorry...
如果那可惡的雞
...if the goddamn chicken...
煮過了頭
...got overcooked.
七名男子在丹麥，對這個關鍵的報告
...seven men in Denmark, to a key defendant here.
- 你找到了嗎？ - 還沒
- Did you find it? - Not yet.
在這裏
There it is.
這裏的某處
It's over here, somewhere.
- 室內設計？ - 後排牆上
- Interior design? - It's on the back wall.
- 先生，要咖啡嗎？ - 好
- Coffee, sir? - Please.
可以把奶精遞給我嗎？
Will you pass the cream?
- 謝謝 - 你買了什麼？
- Thanks. - What did you get?
什麼？
What?
你在看什麼書？
What are you reading?
關於金屬的書
Book about metals.
「鈦的應力斷裂」
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
你做什麼的？
What kind of work you do?
你為何對我看什麼書這麼感興趣？
Lady, why are you so interested in what I read or what I do?
我在店中看過你
I've seen you in the store from time to time.
什麼店？
What store?
軒尼詩和英格斯書店，我在那裏工作
Hennessey + Ingalls. I work there.
呃···
Uh...
如果你不想交談，好的 很抱歉打擾了你
If you don't wanna talk to me, it's okay. I'm sorry I bothered you.
我不想無禮，只是沒認出你
I didn't mean to be rude. I didn't recognize you.
我是銷售員，專營金屬的，我叫尼爾
I work in metals. I'm a salesman. My name's Neil.
我是伊迪
I'm Eady.
你喜歡在書店工作？
You like working there?
是的
Sure.
我買書有折扣，也有我那行需要的書
I get a discount and there's a whole section of books in my area.
是哪一個行業？
What area's that?
平面設計
Graphic design.
我晚上設計信紙及商標
I do, um, letterheads and logotypes at night...
白天在書店工作，直到我能以此謀生
...and the store's a day job till I get enough going.
你為誰設計？
Who do you do that for?
餐廳
Uh, a restaurant.
我設計他們的菜單
I did their menus, and, um...
以及為一個小唱片公司設計
...a small, uh, record label.
鐳射唱片封套，目前已設計了兩張
CDs. I've done two so far.
你在學校學的嗎？
You go to school for that?
是
Heh, yeah.
- 是，帕森設計學院 - 那在哪裏？
- Yeah, I went to Parsons. - Where's that?
紐約市
New York City.
你在這裏住了多久？
How long you been out here?
大約一年
About a year.
喜歡這裏嗎？
You like it?
不算喜歡，我是為了工作才來這裏的
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
- 你住在附近？ - 不
- Live in this neighborhood? - Ah, no...
我住在日落廣場上面
...I live, um, kind of above Sunset Plaza.
其實是···我租了一間小房子
It's actually kind of... It's a little house that I rent.
有點破舊，但景觀很好
And it's just kind of run-down, but a beautiful, beautiful view.
你呢？
What about you?
- 我住在這樓上 - 你真會說笑
- I live up here. - That's very funny.
你的家人最早從哪裏來的？
So where's your family from originally?
嗯···
Um...
他們是蘇格蘭及愛爾蘭裔
I'm Scotch-Irish.
1700年末期移居到美國阿帕拉契
They, um, emigrated to Appalachia in the late 1700s.
你從哪裏來的？
Where are you from?
舊金山灣區
The Bay Area.
家人在那裏？
Are your folks there?
母親很久前死了，我父親··· 我不知道他在哪裏
Uh, my mother died a long time ago, and my father, I don't know where he is.
我有個兄弟在某處
Got a brother somewhere.
我猜你跟家人的關係很緊密吧？
You have a tight family. I can tell.
- 是 - 我就知道
- Yep. - Right?
你說對了
You're right.
是啊···
Yeah...
燈火通明的城市
City of lights.
在斐濟，有一種會發光的海藻 每年浮出水面一次
In Fiji, they have these iridescent algae. They come out once a year in the water.
就像這樣
That's what it looks like out there.
你去過斐濟？
You been there?
沒有，但我終有一天會去
No, I'm going there someday.
是嗎？
Oh, yeah?
你常旅遊？
You travel a lot?
- 是的 - 旅遊使你寂寞？
- Yeah. - Traveling makes you lonely?
我一個人，可是我並不寂寞
I... I'm alone. I am not lonely.
你呢？
You?
很寂寞
I get lonely.
亞伯特！
Albert!
- 該死 - 亞伯特
- Shit. - Albert.
文森，你為何來這裏？
Vincent, what you doing coming here, man?
你瘋了嗎？這裏不是迪士尼樂園
You crazy? This ain't Disneyland.
你昨晚該回我電話的，亞伯特 你去了哪裏？
You were supposed to get back to me last night, Albert. Where the fuck you been?
- 我無法脫身，文森 - 我們侵犯他的民權吧
- I couldn't break free, Vincent. You know. - Let's violate his ass right now.
我幫忙你，你卻不幫我，是這樣嗎？
I do for you, you don't do for me, is that it?
文森，我發誓我整晚在外面
Vincent, man, I swear, I was out all night, man.
為你刺探消息
I'm hitting like one of them flamingo-matador guys.
那和我有什麼關係
Flamingo? That's got nothing to do with me.
我不留痕跡，努力為你找線索
I was cutting it real smooth. I'm generating leads and shit for you.
- 你也知道我很圓滑 - 你胡說
- I'm a dancer, man. You know. - Bullshit.
我傳呼你一整天，我討厭這樣做
I paged your ass all day. I can't stand paging.
你這毒蟲？又吸食安非他命了？
You're a speed freak, jacking methamphetamine again.
我有濫用藥物的問題，有點同情心吧
Where is your empathy, brother? It's a substance-abuse problem.
同情心是昨天
Empathy was yesterday.
今天你在浪費我的時間
Today you're wasting my motherfucking time.
- 文森，聽著 - 你墜入愛河了嗎？
- Vincent, man, look... - Did you fall in love?
告訴我，你昨晚是不是墜入愛河 所以去了別處？
Come on. Did you fall in love last night and you went off somewhere?
- 文森 - 只要告訴我，我會接受這解釋
- Vincent... - Just tell me that. I'll settle for it.
- 我會相信 - 文森
- I'll buy that. - Vincent.
告訴我你所知道的
Give me all you got!
- 文森 - 告訴我你所知道的！
- Vincent... - Give me all you got!
我發誓，我兄弟李察會跟你說
I swear, man, my brother, man. My brother Richard's gonna talk to you.
我聽到他說「李察」？
I heard "Richard"?
- 他會告訴你 - 李察？
- He's gonna talk to you. - Richard?
- 李察 - 李察
- Richard. - Richard.
- 他今晚會見你，我發誓 - 他現在不在這裏？
- He's gonna meet you, I swear, tonight. - He's not here, is he?
- 不在，他今晚會見你 - 今晚？現在不行嗎？
- No, he's gonna meet you tonight. - Tonight? What happened to now?
我懇求他，因為我知道你今早會到來
I... I... I implored him because I knew you was coming this a.m.
- 胡說 - 不，我發誓
- This is a bunch of bullshit. - No, no, I swear.
他說早上不行， 因為他在鳳凰城
He said no because he in Phoenix.
- 啊 - 我發誓，今晚是我僅能做到的
- Ahh. - But this, man, I swear... I swear, man.
我到了鳳凰城後
By the time I get to Phoenix,
他會起程
He'll be risin',
可能留下字條，貼在門上
He'll probably leave a note right on the door.
我盡力了，今晚
Tonight's the best I can do for you, man.
他會和你在阿瓦拉多街的 B J 餐廳見面
You know? He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado...
凌晨二點，去那裏
...at 2 a.m. Be there.
你也要到
You be there too.
文森，我不行，我有事要辦，文森
Vincent, I can't be there, man. I got things to do, Vincent.
- 我有事辦，要到別處去 - 聽好
- I got things to do, places to be. I got... - Hey, hey, hey.
你要去
Be there.
不要浪費我的時間！
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
是什麼買賣？
What is it?
是銀行
It's a bank.
他們星期四會存錢，以便分發給各分行
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution to all the other branches...
讓他們星期五可以支付薪水的支票
...to cover Friday payroll checks.
所以星期四，總行總是放滿現鈔
So on Thursdays, the command branch has got a full whack.
- 在途中下手還是搶劫銀行？ - 銀行，由正門進入
- On the prowl or strong? - Strong. Through the front door.
有多少人？
How many guys?
連司機四人，走進銀行，得手便走
Four, or three plus a driver. Walk in, knock them over, walk out.
你要先拿十萬
And you want a 100,000 advance...
事成後分一成？
...against a 10-percent cut for that?
聽起來像西部牛仔搶劫銀行 他們按警鈴後
Sounds like an address to a cowboy score. They hit the holdup alarms...
我得在警察來臨之前離去，這算什麼？
...I gotta get out before the cops show. What is that?
他們會按三個警鈴
They hit three holdup alarm systems.
兩個透過電話，一個是無線
Two telco and a cellular.
但訊號無法傳送出去，因為
See, but the signals aren't going anywhere because...
你潛進銀行，破壞警報系統的電腦
See, the night before, you cut in and trick out the alarm-system computer...
使電腦及錄影裝置 在你下手的前20分鐘關掉
...to turn itself and the video recorders off 20 minutes before you walk in the door.
你有建築及電子藍圖？
Architectural, electrical-engineering plans?
我都有，圖表、電腦板已經建造好 直接連接到中央處理器
I got all that. Schematics, got the boards already built. They go straight into the CPU.
估計會有多少錢？
What's the estimate?
1210萬到1220萬
12.1, 12.2 million.
我參加
You're on.
恭喜
Congratulations.
讓我告訴你，我如何估計錢的總數 這是我印出來的
And to give you a little idea of where my estimates come from, this is a printout...
沒人知道貨是你的
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
就算如此，照我說的話 保險會全數賠償
Be that as it may, my way you get 100 percent from the insurance company...
以六成價向我們把債券買回
...and take the bonds from us at 60 cents on the dollar...
你可以多賺四成
...and make yourself another 40 percent.
你完全沒有損失，我們大家都受益
Your operation doesn't skip a beat. Everybody makes out.
好，成交
Sure, you got a deal.
很好，因為如果有一方不高興 那就無利潤可言
Good, because there's no percentage if everyone gets their underwear in a twist.
讓你的人給我打電話，安排會面
Yeah, so you have your man call me and we'll set the meet.
好，很好
Yeah, okay.
很高興和你通電話
Nice talking to you.
你要和他們交易？
You gonna deal with these guys?
現在江湖上認為我的東西可以偷
So word's out on the street it's okay to steal my stuff.
我會殺了這幫渾蛋
I'm gonna kill the sons of bitches.
叫哈利給我加納利群島的電子試算表
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets for Canary Islands' offshore.
就像我說的，這些不是估計 是實在數宇
That's not really an estimate. Those are exact figures.
我印出銀行過去兩個月的現金賬
I have a printout of the, uh, cash flow of the bank for the past two months.
- 資料怎麼得來的？ - 送上門的
- How'd you get this information? - Just comes to you.
資料俯拾皆是
This stuff just flies through the air.
他們到處傳送資料
They send information out and it's beamed out all over the place.
只需加以掌握便行，我懂得如何掌握
All you have to do is know how to grab it. See, I know how to grab it.
這是我們要的，1390萬
Um... Okay, here we go. Thirteen-point-nine million.
- 我接了 - 很好
- I bought it. - Good.
我沒說錯吧？
What did I tell you?
拿著
Here.
他同意了，聯絡凡贊，向他收錢吧
We're on. Call Van Zant, collect the money.
- 他怎樣？ - 他是生意人
- How is he? - He's a businessman.
好
Okay.
- 說「酪梨」 - 酪梨
- Avocado. - Avocado.
- 喂？ - 是，喂
- Hello? - Yeah, hello.
克裏斯在我家
Chris is at my place.
- 怎麼了？ - 夫妻爭吵
- What's wrong? - Husband-and-wife stuff.
我讓他睡醒再說
I'll let him sleep it off here.
你怎麼了？
What happened to you?
- 你何時買傢俱？ - 我有空的時候
- When you gonna get some furniture? - When I get around to it.
夏琳要離開我
Charlene's gonna leave me.
為什麼？
Why?
我無法好好養她
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
我們做這麼多買賣還不夠？
With everything we've been doing?
賭場及超級杯使我身無分文
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
- 你何時找個伴？ - 我有空的時候
- When you gonna get an old lady? - When I get around to it.
你有外遇嗎？
You got something else on the side?
沒有固定的
Nothing regular.
她有外遇嗎？
She got something else on the side?
- 沒有 - 你肯定嗎？
- No. - You sure?
是，我肯定
Yeah, I'm sure.
我不知道你在做什麼
I don't know what you're doing.
你記得監獄的吉米馬克溫常說的嗎？
Remember Jimmy MacAwain on the yard used to say:
「你想在江湖混嗎？
You wanna be making moves on the street?
要無牽掛，生活中不能有牽絆
Have no attachments. Allow nothing to be in your life...
可以隨時一走了之
...that you cannot walk out on in 30 seconds flat...
一旦感到風頭不對時」
...if you spot the heat around the corner.
記得嗎？
Remember that?
她是我這人生中最重要的東西
For me, the sun rises and sets with her, man.
是嗎？
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
好
Okay.
今天我們從凡讚那里拿到錢
Today we take delivery of cash from Van Zant...
然後為搶銀行的事付錢給科索
...then I drop our deposit on Kelso for this bank.
銀行？什麼銀行？
Bank? What bank?
那白金的事呢？已經準備好了
What about the platinum thing? It's ready to fall.
那也會進行，然後再搶銀行
That goes too, then the bank.
- 要吃早餐嗎？ - 好
- You want some breakfast? - Yeah.
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
沒事，甜心
Yeah, sugar.
是的
Yeah.
- 真的 - 好
- For real. - Okay.
我會好好地幹
Gonna do good.
一會兒見
I'll see you later.
你是索倫柯？我是唐布裏登
You Solenko? I'm Don Breedan.
葛爾森，我的假釋官口叫我來找你 說你會有工作給我
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to come by here and see if you had a job for me.
- 你對這類工作熟嗎？ - 對，我燒烤很出色
- You're familiar with this kind of operation? - Yeah, man. I'm a great grill man.
好，你去掃廁所，洗碗
Good. Good for you. Here, you'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher...
收拾桌子和倒垃圾
...bus tables and empty the garbage too.
你煩我，我舉報你吸毒酗酒或偷竊
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded, drunk or stealing.
你馬上會被抓回去
And I will violate you back so fast your head will spin.
你給我你薪水的25%作回報
Twenty-five percent of your take-home kicks back to me.
這是規矩，可以問你的假釋官葛爾森
Rules of the game. Call Grierson, check it out.
到後面更衣
Change in the back.
你還再等什麼？
Well, what are you waiting for?
馬裏布股票及投資
Malibu Equity and Investments.
- 找羅傑凡贊 - 請等一等
- Yeah, Roger Van Zant. - Please hold.
我是羅傑凡贊
Yeah, this is Roger Van Zant.
我是來拿東西的
I'm supposed to collect something.
給我你的電話號碼 馬上有人會從別條線打給你
Give me your number, and somebody will call you right back from a different line.
818 - 133 - 6089
818-133-6089.
是
Yep.
我有個包裹要給你
I got a package for you.
森提奈拉街上有個免下車餐廳 明天下午兩點三十
There's a drive-in on Centinela. 02:30 tomorrow.
好，派一個人單獨前來
Okay, just send one man, alone.
- 那人是誰？ - 誰都不是
- Who was that guy? - Nobody.
他是誰？
Who the...? Who...? Who was that guy?
- 誰都不是 - 我要知道他是誰？
- He's nobody. - I gotta know who he is. Who is he?
- 他誰都不是，尼爾 - 聽好，你···
- He's nobody, Neil. - Listen, you...
他是拉斯維加斯合法酒類批發商
He's a legit liquor wholesaler from Las Vegas.
- 艾倫馬西亞諾 - 克裏斯會和你想出解決辦法的
- Alan Marciano. - Chris is gonna straighten it up with you.
- 太遲了，我受不了他了！ - 閉嘴！
- It's too late. I'm sick of it. I'm sick of it! - Shut up!
這樣吧，你再給克裏斯一次機會
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris one last shot.
之後，如果他再犯錯 我會親自掏腰包資助你找地方住
After that, he fucks up, then I will finance setting you up myself...
去哪裏都行
...on my own, anywhere you want.
多明尼克會跟著你，我言出必行
Dominick will go with you. And my word counts.
但現在，你得給他個機會
But right now, you will give him the chance.
清洗一下，回家去
Clean up. Go home.
把錢交出來
Give me all your money.
哪一天，你會因此沒命的
One day you gonna get smoked with that shit.
但殺我的不會是你，傻瓜
Ain't gonna be you, fool.
- 他一個人來，讓他進來 - 是，知道了
- He's coming in alone. Send him through. - Yeah, got it.
文森
Vincent, hey, man.
文森，這是我兄弟李察，李察，文森
Vincent. This is my brother, Richard. Richard, Vincent.
- 李察 - 你好
- Richard. - Yo, it's all right.
你有什麼消息要告訴我？
What have you got for me?
談正題前
Before we even get into that...
海灘附近最近有人偷車，對吧？
...there's this crew ripping rides all along the beach areas, all right?
在爾灣的一家汽車改裝店
Now, the back of a trim shop on Irvine...
如果這個週末去那裏
...if somebody was to pay a little visit this weekend...
會找到兩輛保時捷渦輪 和一輛保時捷911
...they might find two Turbos and a 911 Slope.
你是想消除同業競爭
You're looking to rid yourself of your competition.
我是個好市民
Eh, I'm a good citizen.
我才不信，你有事要告訴我？
I'm Donald Duck. So you got something to tell me or what?
你聽著，朋友
Check this out, coz.
我怎麼知道如果我說出你想知道的事
How do I know if I tell you what you need to know...
你會幫我做我所想做的事
...you're gonna do what the fuck I need to get done?
李察，漢納是可靠的，我們常合作
Richard, man, Hanna is straight up, man. We do business all the time.
雜種，我不是你的朋友
I ain't your coz, you rat motherfucker.
你知道因為我說到做到 但我要先聽你有什麼話要說
And you know because I say so after I hear what the fuck you gotta tell me.
聽好，你明白我在說什麼嗎？
Look here, man. You understand what I'm saying?
我說出來可能會沒命
I can get killed for telling you this shit.
你遛狗時也可能會沒命
Or you're gonna get killed walking your doggie.
好吧
All right.
我在福松監獄中認識了這個人
There's this cat I was locked up with in Folsom.
一起服刑了兩三年，他出獄後我碰上他
Did a couple, two, three years. He got out and I ran into him.
那又怎樣？
And so?
他是一個行動主義者
He's a big fiend for action.
要是他沒說，我也不會去想，可是
Now, if he'd have said nothing, I'd have thought nothing...
他一直說，不斷地對我說他什麼也沒做
...but he goes on and on, running down to me how he ain't been doing nothing...
而且什麼事也沒發生，等等
...and nothing's been going on, and all this bullshit.
那時我便知道，這人參與了不法行為
So right then and there I know this cat's got something going down.
而且是大案子
Pretty fucking great.
亞伯特，你怎麼搞的？
Albert, what's wrong with you?
你要我來這裏，浪費我的時間
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
你在街上見到一個坐過牢的人？
You saw a guy on the street who's an ex-con?
- 是的 - 我實在太意外了
- That's right. - Well, I am over-fucking-whelmed.
你想為此拿兒童榮譽警章嗎？
What do you want for that, a Junior G-man badge?
你會查保時捷的事嗎？
You gonna make the call on them Porsches or what?
他是在說笑嗎？
Is he kidding me?
我告訴你，這滑頭不是鬧著玩的
I'm telling you, this Slick is no joke.
你懂我說的嗎？
You know what I'm saying?
- 什麼？你說什麼？ - 什麼？
- Say what? Say what? - What?
- 你說「滑頭」，那是什麼意思？ - 他常叫別人「滑頭」
- You said, "Slick". What does that mean? - Slick. That's what he calls people, "Slick".
把他的事告訴我
And tell me about him.
他大約六英尺高，有許多監獄的紋身
About 6 feet tall, lot of jailhouse tats.
這裏刺有一頭大孔雀
Got a big-ass peacock right here.
他叫什麼名字？
What's his name?
切利托
Cheritto.
麥克切利托
Michael Cheritto.
自1976年起被捕33次
33 busts since 1976.
11次持械槍搶劫，3次定罪
Eleven for armed robbery, three convictions.
判刑3至5年，在亞地加服刑2年 馬里昂服刑3年
Two out of a three-to-five-year beef in Attica. Three years in Marion.
因誤殺罪在福松監獄服刑5年
Five years in Folsom off a knock-back to involuntary manslaughter.
- 他前科纍纍 - 好
- Jacket's 2 inches thick. - Okay.
- 你們那裏現在有誰？ - 卓克和我，老大，還有史瓦茲
- Who do I have there now? - Drucker and me, boss. And Schwartz.
告訴特別調查組我要完全監控
Tell SIS I want full surveillance.
24小時，日夜不停監視
That's 24 hours. Round the clock, day and night.
從不停歇，一周七日，不斷監視跟蹤他 監聽他的汽車和房子、工作地點
We never close. Open seven days a week. Bug the car, the house, the work.
一舉一動，例如和誰進餐
When he moves or sits, like in a restaurant...
我要所有和他有互動的人的照片
...I want pictures of who he moves and sits with.
調查他們，如果有案底便跟蹤他們 看他們跟誰混
Then run makes on them. They got jackets, I wanna see who they move and sit with.
我要明晚前開始執行
I want it up and running by tomorrow night.
- 把手放在我看得到的地方 - 什麼？
- Put your hands where I can see them. - What?
- 把手放在我看得到的地方 - 好
- Put your hands where I can see them. - All right.
我會告訴你做什麼以及怎樣去做
I tell you what to do, I tell you how to do it.
現在，只用你的右手，只准右手
Now, with your right hand only, your right hand only...
把包裹拿出來，仍過來
...take the package and throw it in here.
該死，你右邊後面有人
Fuck. Behind you. On the right.
羅傑凡贊嗎？
Yeah, Roger Van Zant?
- 是，你是誰？ - 你知道我是誰
- Yeah, who's this? - You know who this is.
是，我知道
Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
我派人送包裹，他沒來電話 一切都好吧？
I sent a guy to deliver the package. He didn't call. Is everything right?
我告訴你，忘了那筆錢
Tell you what, forget the money.
- 什麼？ - 忘了那筆錢
- What? - Forget the money.
呃···
Wh...
你說什麼，數目不少，什麼意思？ 你在做什麼？
It's a lot of money. What are you doing? What do you mean, forget the money?
我在做什麼 ？我在對話筒喃喃自語
What am I doing? I'm talking to an empty telephone...
我不明白
I don't understand.
因為跟我講電話的另一端，是個死人
...because there is a dead man on the other end of this fucking line.
我的天
Oh, my.
- 你喜歡嗎？ - 看我的戒指
- Do you like it? - Look at my ring.
哇喔
Wow.
你之前就知道的？好美
Did you know about this? It's so beautiful.
你真瘋狂
You are insane.
喜歡嗎？
Do you like it?
- 好美 - 是，很棒
- It's beautiful. - Yeah, it's pretty good.
- 別問他從哪裏得來的 - 沒錯
- Just don't ask him where he got it. - Yeah, that's right.
你長大後想做什麼，親愛的？
What do you wanna be when you grow up, honey?
我不知道
I don't know.
她不知道，跟我一樣，我也不知道
She doesn't know. Just like me. I don't know either.
喂？
Hello?
是我
Hi, it's me.
我在想你是否會來電話
Hey. I was wondering if you'd call.
我最近很忙，我可以見你嗎？
I've been busy. Can I see you?
我害怕那只是一夜情
I was afraid that was just the one night, you know?
不，對我來說不是
No, not for me, it wasn't.
我也不是
Yeah, me neither.
我可以來嗎？
Can I fall by?
- 可以 - 好，一會兒見
- Yeah. - Okay, I'll see you in a little bit.
謝謝
Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
該死的聚餐
Goddamn convention.
- 哪一個是滑頭？ - 魁梧的那個
- Which one's Slick? - The wide one.
有兩個監聽器
Got two transmitters.
一個在輪艙裏，備用的在防火牆裏
One's in the wheel well, backup's in the firewall.
是我們的車
Okay, get ready.
- 跟尼爾說晚安了嗎？ - 晚安
- Did you say good night to Neil? - Good night.
金髮的是克裏斯薛哈利斯 特別調查組正派人輪流跟蹤
One with the blond hair is Chris Shiherlis. SIS has got a revolving tail...
和監聽他家的電話
...and hung a wire on the house phone.
切利托開過貴重金屬庫三次
Cheritto's cruised the precious-metals depository three times.
裏面有白金、銀和一些金條
Platinum, silver, and some bullion.
山米和我認為那是他們下一個目標
Sammy and I think that's gonna be their next score.
那獨行俠是誰？
Who's the loner?
我們第一次見他，還沒開始跟蹤他
First time we're seeing him. We're not on him yet.
那趕快開始吧
Well, get on it.
好
Okay.
他們下次不管做什麼案得手 走出大門時
When these guys walk out the door of whatever score they're gonna take next...
鐵定會大吃一驚
...they're gonna have the surprise of a lifetime.
寶貝，我得走了
Hey, baby. Time to go.
我讓你很開心吧？
I showed you a good time, didn't I?
是的
Oh, yeah.
你很棒，很不錯
You fly. You cool.
你騙我，我看得出別人騙我
You're lying to me. I can always tell when people lie to me.
我沒說謊，你狠勇猛
Mm, I ain't lying. You a hot dog.
是個出色的騎士
A regular rodeo rider.
是我年輕的生命中，有過最精采的性交
And this was the monster fuck of my young life.
我現在得回到街上去
Now I got to get my ass street side, sugar.
你沒有說實話的作風
You don't have a truth-telling style.
- 你在說什麼？ - 你不知道是怎麼回事
- What are you talking about? - You don't know what this is.
死神來探望你了
The Grim Reaper's visiting with you.
你去了哪裏？
Where you been?
鵜鶘海灣監獄
SHU at Pelican Bay.
褔松監獄，B座
New Folsom, B-wing.
我是牛仔，吃得了苦
I am a cowboy looking for anything heavy.
比利雷克茨說來找你
Billy Ricketts said come see you.
因此我到這裏來
That is why I am here.
你···
Why don't you...?
你何不給這人打通電話？
Why don't you call this guy?
他經常在徵人
This guy's always putting guys on.
謝了，兄弟
Thank you, brother.
- 我能請你喝一杯嗎？ - 請我喝一杯
- I'll buy you a drink? - Buy me a drink.
- 有什麼好笑的？ - 沒什麼
- What's so funny? - Nothing.
- 很白癡 - 好像有人疏忽了
- It's really dumb. - Something smells negligent.
你們倆天生一對，是怎麼認識的？
You two are perfect for each other. How did you meet?
我念小學時認識一個人
I knew this guy in, uh, grade school.
他叫拉烏，還是什麼的
He was named Raoul, uh... Whatever.
他可以把手指一個一個向上疊
Anyway, the guy could take his fingers and fold them over, one over the other.
然後他會把眼瞼向外翻
Then he'd turn his eyelids inside out...
我忍不住對你上下其手，是真的
I can't keep my hands off you, and that's the truth.
你吸引人的地方就在於你的獸性
That's what's so wonderful about you, in that bestial sort of way.
女人
Woman.
這最好是山崩地裂的大事
This better be earth-shattering.
（一個傅呼 緊急事，105 - 3685）
這是她說的，為拉烏乾杯
That's what she tells us. To Raoul.
- 為拉烏乾杯 - 為拉烏乾杯
- Raoul. - To Raoul.
我是文森漢納
Yeah, Vincent Hanna.
（提供周租）
發現她時是這樣
Here's how we found her.
- 她幾歲？ - 十六、七歲
- How old? - Sixteen, seventeen.
在這裏約六小時
Been here about six hours.
她怎麼死的，瑞秋？
How'd she die, Rachel?
頭部被重擊，大腦血腫，像其他人一樣
Beat her head in, same as the others. Cerebral hematoma.
那是誰？
Who's that?
- 我想是死者母親及家人 - 他們為何到這來？
- Mother and siblings, I guess. - What the hell they doing here?
因為消息走漏，有人認識死者 通知家人
Because it's fucked up. Somebody inside knew the girl and called the family.
好，打開吧
Okay, let's go.
真好
That's nice.
直覺告訴我，化驗精液後，會是同一人
When I run a DNA check on the semen, my intuition says it's coming up the same guy.
所以是連環謀殺案，要由你著手調查
So it's a series, and ending up in your court.
- 兇案組警長有頭緒嗎？ - 還沒有
- Sheriff's Homicide getting anywhere? - Not yet.
- 抓住她 - 放開我，放開我
- Get her. - Get off me. Get off me.
噢
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
- 我的天 - 等等
- Oh, my God. - Hold it, hold it.
- 她在哪裏？ - 冷靜
- Where is she? - Easy, easy, easy.
拜託，別這樣
Please. Please, come on.
- 沒事的 - 是誰幹的？
- It's okay. It's okay. - Who did this?
我的女兒呢？她在哪裏？
Where's my baby? Where is she?
我要知道是怎麼回事
I need to know what happened.
我猜山崩地裂的事的確發生了
I guess the Earth shattered.
你為何不讓博斯高先送你回家？
So why didn't you let Bosko take you home?
我不想掃他們的興 發生了什麼事？
I didn't wanna ruin their night too. What was it?
你不會想知道的
You don't wanna know.
我想知道你為何扳起臉孔
I'd like to know what's behind that grim look.
我不能透露，你是知道的，我們走吧
I don't do that. You know it. Let's go. Come on.
你從沒告訴我，我會被摒除事外
You never told me I'd be excluded.
我們剛在一起時，我告訴過你 你要和我分享
I told you when we hooked up, baby, that you were gonna have to share me...
世上所有的醜行及醜惡的人
...with all the bad people and all the ugly events on this planet.
我同意分享，因為我愛你
And I bought into that sharing because I love you.
你發胖、禿頭、有沒有錢、開公車 我都不在乎，我仍愛你
I love you fat, bald, money, no money, driving a bus. I don't care.
但你得像一般人一樣，偶爾跟我交心
But you have got to be present like a normal guy some of the time.
那才叫分享，這不是分享 我得到的是殘缺不全的東西
That's sharing. This is not sharing, this is leftovers.
我懂了，所以我回家後，應該告訴你
Oh, I see. What I should do is come home and say:
親愛的，你知道嗎？我今天看到一個
Hi, honey, guess what? I walked into this house today...
吸毒男子用微波爐，把他的小孩煮熟
...where this junkie asshole just fried his baby in a microwave...
因為他哭得太大聲，讓我和你分享吧
...because it was crying too loud, so let me share that with you.
讓我們分享此事，而在分享時
Come on, let's share that, and in sharing it...
我們可以宣洩一切不好的事，對嗎？
...we'll somehow cathartically dispel all that heinous shit, right?
錯，你知道為什麼嗎？
Wrong. You know why?
因為你喜歡正常的作法
Because you prefer the normal routine.
我們做愛，然後你不出一語
We fuck, then you lose the power of speech.
因為我得保持我的痛楚
Because I gotta hold on to my angst.
我保存它，因為我需要藉此提高警覺
I preserve it, because I need it. It keeps me sharp, on the edge.
我必須這麼做
Where I gotta be.
你不是和我同住
You don't live with me.
你和死者的殘骸同住
You live among the remains of dead people.
在地面上找線索
You read the terrain.
你尋找死亡的跡象
You search for signs of passing...
找獵物的氣味
...for the scent of your prey...
然後追捕他們
...and then you hunt them down.
這是你唯一投入的事
That's the only thing you're committed to.
其餘的是你經過時留下的爛攤子
The rest is the mess you leave as you pass through.
我不明白的是，我為何不能離開你
What I don't understand is why I can't cut loose of you.
嘿，莉莉安小姐，你好
Hey. Miss Lillian.
我們走吧，寶貝
Let's go, baby.
我見過經理，還是他是老闆？
I met the manager. Is that the boss?
我為他現在每天在做的事而坐牢
I did time for what that motherfucker does every day.
你可以忍受直至找到新工作嗎？
Baby, can you just handle it till we find you something new?
你可以嗎？
Can you do that?
更難忍受的我也捱過
Ain't a hard time been invented that I cannot handle.
你為何和我一起，莉莉安？
What you hanging with me for, Lillian?
因為我以你為榮
Because I'm proud of you.
你以我為榮？
You're proud of me?
你為什麼會以我為榮？
What the hell you proud of me for?
回家吧
Come on home.
- 你去那裏做什麼？ - 我去滑雪
- What were you doing there? - I was skiing.
我試圖滑雪
I was trying to ski.
那就是大家去那裏的原 因，滑雪
That's what people do there. You go skiing...
順便認識別人
...and you meet people.
有個愉快的時光
You try to have a good time.
- 你有愉快的時光嗎？ - 沒有
- Did you have a good time? - No.
為什麼？
Why not?
我不擅交際
I'm not good at meeting people.
你認識了我
You met me.
我沒細想，事情便發生了
Well, that happened without my thinking about it.
可能就是因為這個緣故
Which is why, probably.
不，那是因為你很有魅力
No, it's because you were fine.
伊迪
Eady.
跟我一起去玩
Take off with me for a while.
- 哪裏？ - 紐西蘭
- Where? - New Zealand.
什麼時候？
When?
我不能和你同去 但我可以和你在那會合
I have to go separate, but you could meet me there.
但我的工作，我的···
But my job, my...
我有錢，你不需要賺錢 你可以在那裏開個設計公司，在那工作
I got money. You don't need money. You could set up a studio, do work there.
- 我不知道 - 還要知道什麼？
- I don't know. - What's there to know?
你是不是已經結婚了？
Are you married?
- 什麼？ - 你來去無蹤
- What? - You come and go...
我才沒有結婚
The last thing I am is married.
我的人生正在走下坡，大空白
I'm a needle starting at zero going the other way, a double blank.
可是，突然
Then, all of a sudden...
出現了你這樣的人
...someone like you comes along.
- 你還不夠瞭解我，尼爾 - 我瞭解得夠多了
- You don't know me, Neil. - I know enough.
跟我走
Come with me.
怎麼了，親愛的？
What's wrong, baby?
沒什麼，一切都好，你會去嗎？
Nothing's wrong. Everything's right. Will you go?
會
Yeah.
很好
Good.
- 親愛的 - 你好
- Hey, sweetie. - Hi.
怎麼了？你忘了媽媽會去接你嗎？
What happened? You forget your mom was picking you up?
不是
No.
那是怎麼回事？
So, what's going on?
我想獨自一人待著
I felt like being alone.
好吧，我送你回家
Okay. Come on, I'll drive you home.
- 嘿，麥克 - 嘿，蘿倫
- Hey, Mike. - Hey, Lauren.
有何動靜？
What's happening?
小隊長
Lieutenant. Sir.
傑克森警長想知道有何動靜
Captain Jackson wants to know what's going on.
沒有動靜，不要用無線電
Nothing's going on. Stay off the air.
傑克森是個···
Jackson's a...
（投資級金屬）
好技術
Technique.
芝麻開門，就在那裏
Open sesame. Right there.
他行動了
There he goes.
- 我們離開 - 我快完成了
- We walk. - I'm right there.
我們離開，現在馬上走
We walk! Now! Come on.
他聽到了
He's heard it.
注意
Heads up.
- 一個人出來了 - 等等，警長
- One's coming out. - Hold it, captain.
- 文森，他沒帶走任何東西 - 是，我看到了
- Vincent, he's not carrying anything. - Yeah, I see.
- 行動 - 要等我上司批准
- Here we go. - Not till my boss says so.
文森，他們倆都沒拿東西
Vincent, both of them are not carrying anything.
- 好，讓他們走 - 什麼意思？
- Okay, let them go. - What do you mean?
我們可以逮捕他們
We can take them...
控以何罪？非法入侵？
What are you gonna take them on? Breaking and entry?
你不懂嗎？他們還沒偷東西
They didn't steal anything. Don't you get it?
是輕罪
It gets knocked back to some misdemeanor...
他們坐牢半年便可出獄，不行
...they do six months and they're out. No fucking way.
我會挨上級罵，他們不能走
I'm not taking the heat from my boss. They're not walking.
他們會走，今次行動由我指揮
That's exactly what they're gonna do. They're gonna walk. This is my operation.
我的戰略指揮凌駕你的職位
I have tactical command that supersedes your rank.
他們會離去，你會讓他們走，可惡
They will walk away and you will let them. Fuck.
回去工作
Back to work.
洛杉磯警察？他們從哪裏冒出來的？
L.A.P.D. Gee, what? Where the fuck did this heat come from?
或許他們知道那裏被劫
Maybe it's the score they were onto.
不是因為我們 而是因為那裏以前曾多次被劫
The place, not us. Because it's been hit a couple of times, you know.
假設他們監聽我們的電話住所
Assume they got our phones, assume they got our houses...
假設他們現在正在監視我們的一舉一動
...assume they got us right here, right now as we sit.
假設一切
Everything. Assume it all.
我們要如何付科索銀行的頭期款？
How we gonna buy the bank package from Kelso?
- 那不是問題，我會先墊 - 那凡讚那里呢？
- I'll front that. That's not a problem. - What happens to Van Zant?
警方在追查我們，你想和他開戰嗎？
With the heat we got, do you wanna play World War II in the streets with Van Zant?
不，我想要我的75萬 而他卻可以亳發無傷？
No, I want my 750. And he gets a pass?
我比你們更想殺了凡贊 但他現在成了奢侈品
I got more motivation to whack Van Zant than either of you. He is a fucking luxury.
問題是我們搶銀行遠是離去？
Our problem is, take the bank or split right now?
不要回家，不要收拾東西 什麼都不要做
Do not go home, do not pack, nothing.
30秒後我們各自走我們的陽關道
Thirty seconds flat from now, we are gone on our separate ways.
就此結束
That's it.
克裏斯
Chris.
值得冒險搶劫銀行
The bank is worth the risk.
我需要錢
I need it, brother.
我認為我們應該留下來搶銀行
We should stay and take it down. That's where I come out.
你做什麼我都會跟隨，尼爾，任何事
I roll with you, Neil. Whatever. Whatever.
這次不行，麥克，你要自行決定
No, not on this one, Michael. On this one, you're on your own.
你覺得這是最好的作法嗎？
You figure this is the best thing to do?
這是最好的作法嗎？
This is the best thing to do?
我打算事成後收手，所以對我來說 風險也許值得
I got plans. I'm going away after. So for me the reward is maybe worth the stretch.
但伊蓮很會理財，你存有很多錢
But Elaine takes good care of you. You got plenty put away.
你有基金和地產
You got T-bonds, real estate.
如果我是你，就不會參與這次行動
If I were you, I would be smart. I would cut loose of this.
對我來說，冒險才是我追求的
Well, you know, for me, the action is the juice.
我參加
I'm in.
你也是？
You too?
是，當然
Yeah, sure.
我們動手吧
Let's go.
去他們 的，我們行動吧
Fuck them, let's do it.
好，我們有很多事要做
All right, let's go. We got a lot of work to do.
- 你不能進去 - 你看著
- You can't go in there. - Watch this.
- 不好意思，那··· - 提姆，我再打給你
- Excuse me. That... - Tim, I gotta call you back.
你得先預約
You have to have an appointment.
- 有何貴幹？ - 你是艾倫馬西亞諾？
- Can I help you? - Are you Alan Marciano?
- 是，你是誰？ - 我是誰？
- Yeah, and who the fuck are you? - Who am I?
- 幹什麼 - 文森漢納，洛城警局小隊長
- Hey. Hey. - Lieutenant Vincent Hanna, L.A.P.D.
洛城？這裏是拉斯維加斯 不在你管轄范圉
L.A.? This is Las Vegas. You don't even have jurisdiction here.
我不知道你們以為自己惹到了誰
Hey. Hey, I don't know who the fuck you guys think you're pushing around...
- 我有認識人，好嗎？ - 賭城警方可以拘留你
- ...but I know people here, okay? - Las Vegas P.D. takes you into custody.
引渡你回紐澤西的紐華克
You are extradited to Newark on a New Jersey warrant...
因為三年前，你從北卡羅來納走私香煙
...for smuggling cigarettes up from North Carolina three years ago...
或你可以和我們合作
...or you go to work for us.
簡單明瞭
Cut and dried.
- 就這樣 - 該死
- That is it. - Oh, shit.
夏琳薛哈利斯
Charlene Shiherlis.
- 誰？ - 誰？
- Who? - Who?
誰？你是八哥嗎？一直重複同樣的話
Who? What are you, a fucking owl?
那個上星期每天和你在電話中 淫聲穢語的女子
The lady you been talking dirty to on the telephone every day the last week.
你不能證明我和她有關係
Yeah, you know what? You can't tie me to her.
不需要，你肯定會回去紐澤西的 蠢貨
Who needs to? Your ass is on a plane back to New Jersey, jack off.
我只是···我為和會和她牽扯上？
Oh, man, I just... Why did I get mixed up with that bitch?
因為她的屁股動人！
Because she got a great ass!
你一頭鑽了進去
And you got your head all the way up it.
老天
Jesus.
當我想起屁股，女人的屁股
When I think of asses, a woman's ass...
就會不由自主
...something comes out of me.
- 那麼？ - 小事一樁
- So? - So no big thing.
我只想知道她的丈夫和他們那夥人
All I want is her husband and his whole fucking crew.
你會和這位卓克警探合作
Now, you're gonna work with Sergeant Drucker here.
聖克裏門提路和赫莫沙街
San Clemente Road and Hermosa.
我們在那裏穿過欄柵，從那進入
That's where we cut through the fence. That's the access.
對
Right.
這裏的保安系統不堪一擊
The security systems around here are a joke.
逃走路線一是聖文森湯姆斯橋
St. Vincent Thomas Bridge, that's Escape Route Number 1.
路線二，從安納海姆上110號公路
Number 2, over here, Anaheim to the 110.
- 好 - 好嗎？
- Good. - Okay?
- 很好 - 明白嗎？好，走吧
- Yeah. That's fine. - Got it? Good. Let's go.
他們回頭望向···
They were looking back...
這方向
...in this direction.
貸櫃設施？
A container facility?
- 偷貨車運送？ - 太明顯，對他們來說錢太少了
- For a cartage theft? - Too visible. Too lowball for them.
旁邊是煉油廠，那邊是廢車場
Next door's an oil refinery, over there's a scrap yard.
煉油廠發薪用支票，沒有現金
Refinery only pays by check. No cash around. Same for the scrap yard.
廢車場也一樣
也許他們想偷車輪蓋
Maybe they're stealing hubcaps.
煉油廠和廢車場？
A refinery and a scrap yard.
- 是怎麼回事？ - 這就是我們想要搞清楚的
- What the hell is going on? - That's what we're trying to figure out.
我們以為已經搞清楚了
We thought we had it.
以為已經搞清楚了
Thought we had it.
我知道他們在看什麼
I got an idea of what they were looking at.
- 你們想知道嗎？ - 什麼？
- You wanna know what they're looking at? - What?
這人真了不起，他真行
I mean, is this guy something, or is he something?
這夥人很棒
This crew is good.
你們想知道他們在看什麼嗎？
You know what they were looking at?
什麼？
What?
我們
Us.
洛城警察
The L.A.P.D.
是警察部門
The police department.
我們被認出來了
We just got made.
是的
Yeah.
好
Okay.
好，雜種！
Okay, motherfucker!
科索交出來了嗎？
Kelso come through?
交出來了，藍圖很詳盡
Yeah, you can build a bank with these.
那人姓漢納，叫文森
Name is Hanna. First name Vincent.
我用五百元賄賂了一個警員 漢納在監視你一舉一動
I smeared this sergeant in Vice five yards. Hanna's all over you.
監視所有的車，還有麥克和薛哈利斯的家
He's on all the work cars. Michael's house, Shiherlis'.
沒有監視你，因為不知道你晚上去哪裏
Not yours, they've been losing you at night.
漢納很積極，研究所，海軍陸戰隊
Hanna's a hot dog. Graduate school. Marine Corps.
是劫案及兇案組小隊長，重案組
Lieutenant, Robbery-Homicide, Major Crime Unit.
逮捕了不少人 在芝加哥殺了法蘭基楊德
He's taken down some heavy crews. Blew away Frankie Yonder in Chicago.
他是個瘋子
And he was a fucking maniac.
他之前在緝毒組工作，發生了些問題 離過兩次婚
He was working Narcotics before that. Had some problems, divorced twice.
目前的太太叫賈絲汀 是他下令嚴密監視的
Current wife's Justine. He's why the extra heat.
我的刑警隊警官線人
The Vice sergeant...
說漢納喜歡你
...says Hanna likes you.
認為你是明星，能做這做那
Thinks you're some kind of star. You do this sharp, you do that sharp.
行事很有技巧，很聰明
Look how sharp this guy is to figure that.
這一點也不好笑，結過三次婚
Funny as a heart attack, man. Three marriages.
你認為是為什麼？他喜歡待在家？
What the fuck do you think that means? He likes staying home?
這代表他是那種
Means the man is one of those guys out there...
整晚工作的人，很投入
...prowling around all night, dedicated.
有他和警方監視，取消搶劫銀行吧
With this guy and this much heat, you should pass.
值得冒險一試
It's worth the stretch.
他可以出錯，而你一次都不能出錯
This guy can hit and miss. You can't miss once.
你確定嗎？
You sure?
我確定
I'm sure.
我們去車庫吧
Let's go to the garage.
賈絲汀
Justine.
賈絲汀？
Justine?
我們要去哪裏？
Where we going?
- 好吧，你要去哪裏？ - 外出
- Okay, where are you going? - Out.
- 他們用什麼頻道？ - 機動組第9頻道
- What are you on? - TAC 9.
他們在405號公路，往機場方向北走
They're northbound out LAX on the 405. We got four ground units.
我是文森漢納，在18號機 有什麼動靜？
This is Vincent Hanna in Air 18. Who have I got?
文森，我是40號機的 J J ，李察葛洛佛跟我在一起
Hey, Vincent, it's JJ. I'm in Air 40. Richard Glover's with me.
車在105號公路東行 接近110號公路交叉
It's on the 105 eastbound approaching the 110 interchange.
- 交替跟蹤？ - 是，前有兩輛車，在他後面有三輛
- You running a revolving tail? - Yeah, I got two units in front, three behind.
好的，要其中一輛在佛蒙特州的匝道上接我
Okay, have one of them pick me up at the Vermont on-ramp.
走吧
Let's go.
我離他100碼嗎？太近還是太遠？
Am I 100 yards, or what? Am I close or far, or what?
他離你300碼，在中間車道
Three hundred yards, center lane.
你好嗎？
How you doing?
我請你喝杯咖啡如何？
What do you say I buy you a cup of coffee?
- 好，走吧 - 跟我走
- Yeah, sure. Let's go. - Follow me.
你在福松監獄七年
Seven years in Folsom.
單獨囚禁三年
In the hole for three.
之前在麥克尼爾監獄
McNeil before that.
麥克尼爾真的像他們說的那樣不堪嗎？
McNeil as tough as they say?
你想當監獄學者嗎？
You looking to become a penologist?
你想再坐牢嗎？
You're looking to go back?
我追捕了一些想犯錯再度入獄的人
You know, I chase down some crews guys just looking to fuck up,
你是那種人嗎？
get busted back. That you?
你逮捕的人鐵定是些飯桶
You must've worked some dipshit crews.
我逮捕各式各樣的人
I worked all kinds.
你認為我是尋刺激行劫酒鋪
You see me doing thrill-seeking liquor-store holdups...
胸膛上刺著「天生輸家」的人嗎？
...with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
- 我不認為 - 對
- No, I do not. - Right.
我不會再坐牢
I am never going back.
那麼就別再搶劫
Then don't take down scores.
我做我擅長做的事，搶劫
I do what I do best, I take scores.
你做你擅長做的事，阻止我這樣的人
You do what you do best, trying to stop guys like me.
你從不想過正常生活？
So you never wanted a regular-type life?
那是什麼？烤肉和看球賽嗎？
What the fuck is that? Barbecues and ball games?
是的
Yeah.
- 像你一樣正常的生活嗎？ - 我的生活？不，我的生活
- This regular-type life like your life? - My life? No, my life...
我的生活一塌糊塗
No, my life's a disaster zone.
我的繼女情緒深受困擾
I got a stepdaughter so fucked up...
因為她的生父是個大渾蛋
...because her real father is this large-type asshole.
我和太太，我們的婚姻正面臨破碎邊緣
I got a wife. We're passing each other on the down slope of a marriage...
這是我的第三度婚姻
...my third...
因為我把所有時間都花在 追捕像你這樣的人
...because I spend all my time chasing guys like you around the block.
那就是我的生活
That's my life.
有人曾對我說：
A guy told me one time:
「要了無牽掛
Don't let yourself get attached to anything...
隨時可以一走了之
...you are not willing to walk out on in 30 seconds flat...
一旦感到風頭不對時」
...if you feel the heat around the corner.
如果你想抓我，我行動時你也行動
Now, if you're on me, and you gotta move when I move...
你要如何才能保有婚姻呢？
...how do you expect to keep a marriage?
這說法很有趣
Well, that's an interesting point.
你是出家人嗎？
What are you, a monk?
我有女伴
I have a woman.
你怎麼告訴她？
What do you tell her?
我說我是推銷員
I tell her I'm a salesman.
那麼你如果見我從街角走來
So then, if you spot me coming around that corner...
你會離開她？
...you're just gonna walk out on this woman?
不告而別？
Not say goodbye?
要有這樣的自律
That's the discipline.
那心靈會很空虛，不是嗎？
That's pretty vacant, no?
正是如此
Yeah, it is what it is.
不這樣做，我們還是另找職業吧
It's that, or we both better go do something else, pal.
我不懂做別的
I don't know how to do anything else.
我也不懂
Neither do I.
- 我不想 - 我也不想
- I don't much want to either. - Neither do I.
我不斷重複這夢境
You know, I have this recurring dream.
我坐在偌大的餐宴席上
I'm sitting at this big banquet table...
我調查過的兇殺案受害人全部出席
...and all the victims of all the murders I ever worked are sitting at this table...
他們用漆黑的眼珠子瞪著我
...and they're staring at me with these black eyeballs...
因為他們頭部中槍出血
...because they got eight-ball hemorrhages from the head wounds.
這些屍體發脹
And there they are, these big balloon people...
因為他們被殺兩周後 我才在床下發現他們
...because I found them two weeks after they'd been under the bed.
鄰居報警說有惡臭
The neighbors reported the smell...
他們全部出席，坐在那裏
...and there they are, all of them just sitting there.
他們說什麼？
What do they say?
沒說話
Nothing.
- 沒人說話？ - 沒人
- No talk? - None.
他們無話可說
Just... They don't have anything to say.
我們彼此望著對方
See, we just look at each other.
他們望著我，就這樣，夢境就是這樣
They look at me. And that's it, that's the dream.
我有夢到自己溺水
I have one where I'm drowning.
我得叫醒自己起來呼吸 否則會死在夢裏
And I gotta wake myself up and start breathing, or I'll die in my sleep.
你知道這象徵什麼嗎？
You know what that's about?
知道，要有足夠的時間
Yeah. Having enough time.
- 足夠時間，做你想做的事？ - 是的
- Enough time to do what you wanna do? - That's right.
- 你現在這樣做？ - 還沒有
- You doing it now? - No, not yet.
我們坐在這裏
You know, we're sitting here...
你和我，像兩個普通人
...you and I, like a couple of regular fellows.
彼此做必須做的事
You do what you do, and I do what I gotta do.
現在我們見過面
And now that we've been face to face...
如果要我在案發現場殺你，我不會喜歡
...if I'm there and I gotta put you away, I won't like it.
但我告訴你
But I'll tell you...
如果是在你和讓你殺死···
...if it's between you and some poor bastard...
妻子會成寡婦的人當中作選擇
...whose wife you're gonna turn into a widow...
兄弟，沒命的會是你
...brother, you are going down.
換另一面想
There's a flip side to that coin.
如果你逼得我走投無路 我不得不殺你呢？
What if you do got me boxed in and I gotta put you down?
因為不論如何，你都不能阻止我
Because no matter what, you will not get in my way.
是的，我們見過面
We've been face to face, yeah...
但我會亳不猶疑殺你，一秒也不會遲疑
...but I will not hesitate. Not for a second.
也許真會這樣
Maybe that's the way it'll be.
或是誰知道呢？
Or who knows?
也許我們永遠不會再見
Or maybe we'll never see each other again.
他們擺脫了我們
They dumped us.
什麼？
What?
- 他們逃脫了 - 什麼意思，逃脫了？
- They dumped us. - What do you mean, they dumped us?
克裏斯逃脫了
Chris slipped his tail.
他沒跟夏琳談及搶劫的事
He doesn't talk about scores with Charlene...
所以無法從馬西亞諾那邊得到資料 我試過了
...so there's nothing for me to get from Marciano. I tried.
- 切利托？ - 也一樣
- What about Cheritto? - Same.
監聽詢答機被放到 往聖克裏門提的公車上
Transponders got put on a bus to San Clemente.
- 他們擺脫我們所有的監視？ - 是的，同一時間，晚上九點
- They dumped all our surveillance? - Yeah, at the same time. 9 p.m.
我半小時前才和麥考利喝咖啡！
I had coffee with McCauley half an hour ago!
我們有跟蹤，但之後麥考利開到機場
We were on you. Then McCauley drives into LAX...
我們無法靠近監視，因為飛行跑道
...where surveillance can't fly over because of flight paths.
他的車子仍在，人不見了
His car's still there. He's gone.
有誰知道他們在哪裏嗎？
Does anybody have any idea where the fuck these people are?
他有聯絡嗎？
You hear from him yet?
沒有，這讓我更不安，他在哪裏？
Not a thing. And not hearing bothers me more. Where's this guy?
這個人，我們用他，他說他認識麥考利
This guy here. We put him on. Says he knows McCauley.
你是誰？
Who are you?
韋恩葛羅，我的名字是韋恩葛羅
Waingro. My name's Waingro.
我躲在這辦公室好多天了 你跟他很熟嗎？
I've been living in this office day and night. How well do you know him?
我們一起做了不少大買賣
Oh, we took some major scores together.
他為何還沒找上我？
How come I haven't heard from him?
他可能在忙，但他做事很徹底
Well, he's probably busy right now, but he's real thorough.
- 他不會忘記你的 - 真令人安心
- He ain't gonna forget about you. - Oh, that's reassuring.
我可以做點事
Well, I got some moves I could make here.
可能對你會很有幫助
Probably be a big help to you.
認得那個在烤肉的人嗎？
You recognize the grill man?
- 不認得 - 福松D座，和多比羅許同一囚室
- No. - Folsom. D-block. Housed with Dobie Rush.
- 我還沒休息 - 西斯科和潘喬沒上班
- Ain't got my break yet, man. - Cisco and Pancho didn't show.
倒垃圾、拖餐廳後面的地
Haul out the garbage. Mop up the back.
稍後再休息
Take your break later.
人渣，送出去吧
Piece of shit. Pick up.
他在哪裏？
Where the hell is he?
- 我想弄一輛工作車 - 我也是
- I wanted to check the slot for a work car. - So did I.
是？
Yeah?
等一等
Hang on.
- 喂 - 喂
- Yeah. - Hey.
用普通電話，打103 - 7206
Use a landline. Call me at 103-7206.
好
All right.
- 你在哪裏？ - 到處有警察監視我
- Where are you? - There's cops all over me, man.
我無法擺脫他們
They're on me like a cheap suit. I can't dump them.
- 他們知道你看見他們了？ - 不，他們並行跟蹤
- After the fact you spotted them? - No, no. They're doing parallels.
我可以再試著擺脫他們
I can try to dump them again.
我們怎麼知道你是否擺脫了 如果沒有，你會引他們來找我們
How are we gonna know if you did? If you didn't, you'll draw them to us.
去文杜拉，把他們帶離這裏
Head for Ventura. Pull them out of here.
對不起，我真不想讓你失望的
All right. Hey, I'm sorry, man. Last thing I wanna do is let you down.
快點
Come on, man.
送出去
Pick up.
- 尼爾，你好嗎？ - 你好嗎？
- Hey, hey, Neil, man. What up? - What's up, brother?
你在這裏做什麼？
Man, what you doing here?
我在找可以應付警方跟蹤的司機
What I am doing is I'm looking for a driver who can handle scanners and a radio.
現在就需要
Right now, today.
你還記得怎麼做嗎？
You remember the drill?
記得
Yeah, man, sure.
你可以嗎？
You cool?
你知道我可以
Oh, man, now, you know I'm cool.
你現在就回答我，行或不行
One answer, yes or no. Right now.
好的，去他的，我答應
Yeah, man. Fuck, yeah. You're on.
五分鐘後到後面
Out back in five.
- 什麼燒焦了？什麼燒焦了？ - 不是我
- What's burning? What's burning? - Nothing I'm doing.
搞什麼？
What is this?
你要去哪裏？
Where do you think you're going?
剛拿到手康丁斯基初版的 《顏色的理論》
Just came across a first edition of Kandinsky's Theory of Color.
不，狀況良好
Yeah. No, it's in good condition.
該船不肯停駛或用無線通訊回答
And it will not stop or answer radio communication.
身長180英尺的船隻叫作菁英一號
The 180-foot vessel is called Jin Yin Number 1...
涉嫌走私中國移民
...and is suspected of smuggling Chinese illegal aliens.
週六被巡邏機發現
It was spotted Saturday by patrol aircraft.
- 趴下 - 別動！別給我動！
- Stay down. - Don't move! Don't fucking move!
舉起手來！舉起手來！舉起手！
Put your hands in the air! Put your hands in the air! Put them up!
跪下！快跪下
Down, down! Get on your knees.
- 給我鑰匙 - 跪下
- Give me the keys. - Get on your knees.
快跪下！
Get on your knees!
過去那邊！跪下
Hey. Hey! Get over there. Get the fuck... Get down.
轉身！把手放在背後！
Turn around! Put your hands behind you. Behind you!
跪下！
Get down! Stay down!
跪下！跪下！你這混蛋
Get down! Get down! Down, you stupid son of a...
- 快跪下 - 鑰匙！鑰匙！鑰匙！
- Down! Down, now! - Keys! Keys! Keys!
你們全部跪下
All of you stay down.
我們不想傷人，只要銀行的錢 不要你們的錢
We want to hurt no one. We're here for the bank's money, not your money.
你們不會有損失，銀行有政府的保險
Your money's insured. You're not gonna lose a dime.
想想你的家人，別冒生命危險逞英雄
Think of your families. Don't risk your life. Don't try and be a hero.
我要你們坐在地上，手放頭上
Right now I want you to sit on the floor and put your hands on your head.
不舒服或心臟不好的，可以靠牆
Anybody feels sick, anybody got heart trouble, go ahead and lean against the wall.
- 給我鑰匙 - 什麼鑰匙？
- Give me the key. - What key?
跪下！繼續跪著！
Get down and stay down!
坐下，別動，讓傷口流血吧
Sit there. Sit there. Don't move. Let it bleed.
跪下！
Get down!
嘿，嘿！
Hey. Hey!
低下頭！
Put your head down.
- 再看我一次，我會殺了你 - 跪下
- Look at me again, I'll kill you. - Stay down. Down.
- 把頭低下！ - 跪下，跪下
- Put your head down! - Get down. Get down.
- 卡薩爾 - 是
- Hey, Casals. - Yeah.
你們在調查尼爾麥考利？
You guys working a case on a Neil McCauley?
機密線人休班尼打來說什麼 關於搶劫銀行的
This CI, Hugh Benny, called in about a bank they're looking at or something.
文森
Vincent.
上午十一點半遠東國家銀行！
Far East National Bank, 11:30!
在第五街和費古洛街設路障
I want a block at Figueroa and 5th...
往北的花街及第六街也設路障
...and I want a block northbound Flower at 6th.
他們出來了
They're already coming out.
要在車上捉他們 等他們全上車後才動手
Okay, we're gonna have to take them in the car. Wait till they are all in.
開槍要俐落，不要傷及無辜
Get clean shots. Watch your background.
- 警察！走開！ - 發生什麼事？
- Police! Move! - What's going on?
走開！蹲下
Move. Move. Get down.
小心
Look out.
- 快走開 - 洛杉磯警察局，蹲下
- Move it, come on. - L.A.P.D. Get down.
快走開，蹲下
Move it. Down, down, down.
我們成功了，尼爾？
We did it, right, Neil? Huh?
快走！
Move!
蹲下
Get down.
該死！
Fuck. Fuck!
快上車！
In the car!
快開！
Go! Go! Go!
- 混蛋！ - 快開 ！
- Son of a bitch! - Go, go!
快走！
Go!
快起來
Come on. Come on.
快把他帶走
Get him out of here.
快蹲下！
Get down! Now!
該死
Shit.
快走開！蹲下！快走開！快叫他們蹲下
Out of the way! Down! Out of the way! Get them down! Now, now!
不，走開，走開
No, out of the way. Out of the way.
媽媽？媽媽！
Mommy? Mommy!
親愛的，過來
Come here, honey.
快過來
Come on, honey.
我抱著你，沒事了
I got you. It's okay now.
南加州今天發生慘劇 銀行劫案禍廷大街
Tragedy in a Southland neighborhood today. A bank robbery spilled out into the street.
克勞蒂亞紐曼在現場，她有最新的消息 克勞蒂亞？
Claudia Newman, live on the scene. She has the latest. Claudia?
今天下午，這附近因為搶劫銀行未遂 發生了恐怖的事件
This afternoon, this neighborhood was terrorized by a bank holdup gone wrong.
街上滿是行人、警方和劫匪
With the streets full of mid-day shoppers and kids, police and armed robbers...
- 不好意思，酒保？ - 等一下，小姐
- Excuse me, bartender? - One minute, lady.
搶劫，追逐，最終死亡
...robbery, pursuit and, finally, death.
一件銀行搶劫案震驚了洛杉磯地區
A Los Angeles neighborhood is shaken by a bank robbery...
最後以兇殺及恐懼告終
...that ended in homicide and terror.
其中一個嫌犯，麥克切利托 也是四名劫匪之一
One suspect, Michael Cheritto, is one of four men involved in the foiled robbery.
- 在現場當場死亡 - 要喝什麼？
- He died at the scene. - What can I get you, miss?
另外一名重傷不治的嫌犯唐納布裏登···
Also fatally wounded, suspect Donald Breedan...
小姐？
Miss?
當時警方和嫌犯正在激烈對峙
...during the extensive gunfire between police and suspects.
好了，按住他
All right, hold him. Hold him.
- 好，好 - 沒事
- All right. All right. - It's all right.
- 怎樣？ - 他失血和受驚
- So? - Well, he's got blood loss and shock.
我會給你四分之一粒嗎啡止痛 皮下注射
I'm gonna give you quarter-grain morphine for the pain. Subcutaneous injection.
告訴我狀況
Bottom line.
主要是組織受損，那是好事 但他的鎖骨骨折
It's mostly tissue damage, which is good, but his clavicle's fractured.
- 可以讓他休息一陣子嗎？ - 六、七個小時
- Can he rest for a while? - Six, seven hours.
- 不能多？ - 只能這樣
- That's it? - That's it.
- 脫下你的襯衫 - 什麼？
- Take off your shirt. - What?
脫下你的襯衫
Take off your shirt.
這是女兒給我的父親節禮物
My... Look, my daughter gave it to me for Father's Day.
我才不管是誰給你的，脫下來
I don't give a shit who gave it to you. Take it off.
克裏斯
Chris. Hey.
克裏斯，聽我說
Chris, listen to me.
奈特會來接你，帶你去他家
Nate's gonna pick you up. He's gonna take you to his place.
- 夏琳在哪？ - 我們得離開這裏
- Where's Charlene? - We gotta get out of here.
晚間新聞一直在播報我們
We're all over the 6:00 news.
- 我們得離開這裏 - 沒有她我不走
- We gotta get out of here. - I'm not going without her.
你考慮一下，我們在奈特家見
Think about that. I will meet you at Nate's.
你去哪裏？
Where are you going?
我得知道我們的逃走路線 是否也一同被洩漏了
I gotta find out if our out got spilled along with every other damn thing.
是誰告密的？
Who did it?
有誰沒參加？
Who wasn't there?
崔荷
Trejo.
奈特家見
I'll see you at Nate's.
- 是 - 你仍想要我嗎？
- Yeah. - Yeah. You still want me?
你馬上來這裏接我和多明尼克
You come down here right now and you get me. Dominick and me. Okay?
好的，寶貝，我兩小時候到，好嗎？
Okay, baby, okay. I'll be there in two hours, all right?
- 好嗎？ - 好
- Okay? - All right.
你真該死，克裏斯，你真該死
Goddamn you, Chris. Goddamn you.
- 你會坐飛機去洛杉磯 - 太好了
- You're on a plane for Los Angeles. - Great.
你為何這樣做？發生了什麼事？
Why'd you do it? What happened?
- 他們逼我的 - 誰？
- They made me. - Who?
安娜呢？
Where's Anna?
她死了
She's dead.
麥克和代替你的布裏登也死了
So is Michael and Breedan, the guy who stood in for you.
- 誰做的？是誰做的？ - 他們以安娜要挾
- Who did it? Who did it? - They had Anna, man.
是誰？
Who had her?
韋恩葛羅
Waingro.
他一個人嗎？
On his own?
- 他替人··· - 誰？
- For someone. - Who?
他替另一個人工作
The other he worked for.
贊
Zant.
- 凡贊？ - 是
- Van Zant? - Yeah.
凡贊
Van Zant.
- 你確定嗎？ - 凡贊
- Are you sure? - Van Zant.
你有說出我們會怎樣逃走嗎？
Did you say anything about how we're getting out?
- 應該沒有，尼爾 - 快想
- I don't think so, Neil. - Come on.
我不記得，尼爾
I don't remember, Neil.
- 我去叫救護車 - 我撐不過去的
- I'll call a medic. - I'm not gonna make it.
我亳無感覺
I can't feel nothing.
我的安娜死了
My Anna's gone.
她死了
She's gone.
別這樣扔下我，尼爾，求求你，兄弟
Don't leave me like this, Neil. Please, holmes.
別這樣扔下我
Don't leave me like this.
- 是？ - 奈特
- Yeah? - Nate.
你用行動電話嗎？用普通電話
You on a cellular? Use a hard line.
這是新的電話
It's a new one.
他住在恩西諾區山景台
The guy lives on Hillside Terrace, Encino.
- 10725號 - 10725號，好
- 10725. - 10725, okay.
- 克裏斯呢？ - 他和我一起在我家中
- Chris? - He's with me, at my place.
接下來查出韋恩葛羅在哪，好嗎？
Next, Waingro, okay?
你有時間嗎？
You got the time?
我會抽空的，我要新的逃走路線
I'll make time, and I need a new out laid on.
你怎麼知道舊路線被洩漏了？
How do you know it's blown?
我怎麼能保證沒有呢？
How can I trust it?
好的
Okay, you got it.
保重
Stay healthy.
夏琳薛哈利斯
Charlene Shiherlis.
卓克在威尼斯區有地方可以讓她藏身
Drucker's got a safe house in Venice to stash her in.
尼爾的逃走方法 這裏處理完後，開始詢查
Our Neil's transportation. When we're done here, get on the phone.
有人正在替他安排
Somewhere, someone's trying to put it together for him.
你不認為麥考利已經有計劃？
You don't believe McCauley already had a getaway?
當然有，但他需要另一個計劃 要是你，你還會相信原先的計劃嗎？
Sure he did. Now he needs another one. Would you trust yours after this afternoon?
這告密的人，哪裏找到他的？
This rat motherfucker, where did we get him?
他是機密線人，通報搶劫銀行
He's a CI for a burglary cop. Called in the tip on the bank.
至於尼爾麥考利 我們還剩多少時間？
On Neil McCauley, how much time we got?
他有八到十小時安排新的逃走路線 之後就遠走高飛了
Eight, 10 hours for him to set up a new out. After that, he's gone.
拜拜啦
Bye-bye. Bam.
你向我們告發麥考利，你怎麼知道？ 是誰告訴你的
You ratted McCauley to us. How'd you know? Who told you?
誰告訴你的？你這告密者！
Who told you, you rat motherfucker?
是誰？
Who?
康納利針對墨菲 墨菲和萊格特一同對抗
Connelly back in for Murphy. Murphy with Leggat right there with him.
墨菲從網後準備出招
Murphy tees it up behind the net...
米勒跑到前頭，墨菲與裁判爭辯
...Miller out front. Now here's Murphy with the referee...
韋恩葛羅在哪裏？
Waingro, where is he?
- 他在哪裏？ - 我怎麼知道？
- Where is he? - How the hell would I know?
這裏有些什麼？
Well, what do we have here, hmm?
這裏漂亮嗎？漂亮
Isn't this pretty? It's pretty.
- 你這卑鄙小人 - 你告訴我你想脫離目前困境
- You slimy piece of shit. - You told me you wanted out from under.
你快嚇死了，對吧？ 你想脫身吧？這就是出路，夏琳
You're scared to death, right? You want out? This is out, Charlene.
- 你得到了什麼好處？ - 我···蠢女人
- Yeah, what's your end? - I... You stupid broad.
- 我怎麼會被牽連？ - 別衝動
- How'd I get into this? - Hey, hey, hey. Easy.
你聽到了
You heard me.
她飽受驚嚇，幫她倒杯酒
She had a rough ride. Why don't you fix her a drink or something?
- 去櫥櫃看看 - 去她的
- Look in the cabinet above the sink. - Fuck her.
- 你最好進了櫥櫃就不要出來 - 好，乖
- You'd better get in there and stay in there. - All right, all right.
聽著
Well, lookie here.
我叫卓克警探，洛杉磯警察局兇案組
My name is Sergeant Drucker, L.A.P.D. Homicide.
- 你要讓多明尼克在臥房睡嗎？ - 他和我一起
- You wanna put Dominick in the bedroom? - He stays with me.
來吧
There we go.
現在怎樣？
So, what now?
他說的對，你想脫身？這是出路
Well, he's right, because you want out, this is out.
- 你覺得你會出賣克裏斯 - 廢話
- You believe you have to betray Chris. - No shit.
對，你得這樣做
That's right. You would have to.
如果你不出賣克裏斯 多明尼克會是受害人
See, if you don't betray Chris, you victimize Dominick.
因為當你因從犯而入獄，他會變成孤兒
Because he becomes an orphan when you go to prison as an accessory...
你沒有父母可以照顧他
...because you got no living parents to take him.
他會被送去寄養家庭、少年感化院
So he ends up state-raised in foster homes, juvenile facilities.
之後他會偷車
Then he steals a car.
然後不斷入獄成為真正的罪犯
Then he winds up in gladiator academies like Chino and Tracy.
毀了一生
Fucked for life.
你是過來人，知道會有何下場
You know what happens, because you've been there.
多明尼克還沒機會選擇生活 但克裏斯有
Dominick didn't get a chance yet to choose his life, but Chris did.
你如果供出克裏斯，你不會有案底
If you give up Chris, you get off clean.
為孩子這樣做，你才能撫養他
You can do it for your kid, so you can raise him.
- 你還要推銷什麼東西？ - 各種東西
- What else are you selling? - All kinds of shit.
但我不用說服你，因為我是對的
But I don't have to sell this and you know it, because this kind of shit here sells itself.
好，丹尼，最新消息
Okay, Danny, here's an update.
- 卓克在二線 - 小隊長，等一下
- Drucker's on Line 2. - Lieutenant, hold on for a second.
小隊長，卓克在另一個電話線上
Lieutenant, I have Drucker on the other line.
三人通話吧
Oh, well, conference him in.
- 說吧 - 文森，是我
- Go ahead. - Vincent, it's me.
你的答案是什麼？
I want an answer. What's it gonna be?
我們準備好了，她會打電話
We're set here. She'll make the call.
好的，情況是這樣
Okay, that's good. Here's the deal here.
休班尼已經改過自新 成為洗心革面的好公民
Hugh Benny has reformed his wayward life and become a born-again good citizen.
顯然一個叫韋恩葛羅的牛仔 向我們出賣尼爾
Apparently, Neil got sold out to us by this cowboy named Waingro.
韋恩葛羅曾是尼爾的手下
Waingro used to be a part of Neil's crew...
後來替一個叫凡讚的洗錢人工作
...then he went to work for a money launderer named Van Zant.
小組正在凡贊家 因為他今晚較早前被殺
Units are at Van Zant's house as we speak because he got shot dead earlier tonight.
如果尼爾還有誰要對付 那就是韋恩葛羅
Now, if Neil goes after anybody else, it's gonna be Waingro.
韋恩葛羅入住機場馬奎斯酒店套房
Waingro just got himself a suite at the airport Marquis...
化名「詹姆森」，他現在在那
...under the name "Jameson". He's there now.
我要你把這消息告訴保釋人、組頭
I want you to get that to bail bondsmen, bookies...
警員及線人
...assignment officers and snitches in County.
任何可以把消息傳開的人
Anyone you can think of who'll put it on the street.
派人到酒店，並每隔半小時 親自收聽他們的無線電
Deploy a team at the hotel and personally check their come every 30 minutes.
因為也許尼爾會去找他，你感覺如何？
Because maybe Neil will go for him. Okay? How you feeling?
- 渾身是傷，但我會熬過 - 好
- Banged up, but I'll live. - Okay.
他在這裏
He's here.
尼爾還沒走
Neil is still here.
我可以感覺到
I can feel it.
但他會留多久？
But for how long?
最多七八個小時
Seven, eight hours, max.
你幹了什麼？
What did you do?
- 是你做的？ - 我沒做的比較重要，我不是賣金屬的
- That was you? - It's what I don't do, I don't sell metal.
原本計劃順利，你之後離開 但現在出了點麻煩
Would have been okay, you fly out after. Now it's jammed.
- 我們要一起走 - 那些和你一起的人呢？
- Now we gotta go together. - Those other people were with you?
我的朋友，麥克
My friend, Michael...
他知道冒的險有多大 他可以選擇不要參加
...he knew the risks. He didn't have to be there.
不入虎穴，焉得虎子
It rains, you get wet.
快收拾東西，我們離開
Get packed and let's go.
伊迪
Eady.
你為何這樣對我？
Why did you do this to me?
你到底是誰？
Who are you?
會沒事的，你懂嗎？沒事的
It's gonna be all right. You understand? It'll be all right.
不會有事的
It's gonna be all right.
好
Right.
這地址D層18單位 有一輛雪佛蘭科邁羅
There's this Camaro at this address, Level D, Slot 18.
這裏有現金
Here's some cash.
這事什麼時候會結束？
When's it over?
22小時後
22 hours from now.
- 我們就可以脫身 - 你何時會讓我離開？
- Then we get out of here clean. - When will you let me leave?
你想走？現在可以走，門在那裏
Go now. You want out? There's the door.
你之後會讓我離開嗎？
Will you let me leave later?
情況會不同
It will be different.
你明白嗎？
Do you understand?
準備好了
It's ready.
文森
Vincent.
這是我的朋友雷夫
This is my friend Ralph.
你沒有告訴我你有···
You didn't tell me you were...
- 我的天 - 蘿倫呢？
- Oh, my God. - Where's Lauren?
- 她在麗莎貝絲家 - 聽著，這事和我無關
- She's at Lisa-Beth's. - Look, this has nothing to do with me.
- 我不知道她結婚了，我很抱歉 - 你抱歉什麼，坐下
- I didn't know. I'm terribly sorry. - What are you sorry about? Sit down.
你不生氣嗎？
Don't you even get angry?
我生氣，是的
I'm angry, yeah.
我很生氣，雷夫
I'm very angry, Ralph.
你知道嗎？如果你想要上我太太 而且她同意，你可以上
You know, you can ball my wife if she wants you to.
你可以躺在她的沙發上
You can lounge around here on her sofa.
可以待在她前夫的
In her ex-husband's...
低科技、後現代主義的荒謬家中 如果你想要的話
...dead-tech, post-modernistic, bullshit house, if you want to...
但你不能看我該死的電視機
...but you do not get to watch my fucking television set!
有沒有搞錯！
For God's sake.
把電視機放下
Put the television set down.
- 我從沒對你不忠，賤人 - 也許你應該
- I never cheated on you, bitch. - Maybe you should have.
- 我應該嗎？ - 這不是你自找的嗎？
- I should have? - In a way, you're a party to this.
對，是我要雷夫干你 因為這樣我會很開心
Oh, yeah. I made Ralph fuck you because it makes me feel good.
我們的處境很荒謬
Our situation is absurd.
- 聽著，也許我應該··· - 閉嘴，雷夫，坐下！
- Look, maybe I should... - Shut up, Ralph. Sit down!
為什麼總是我得搞清楚我們之間的事 並向你解釋？你做了什麼？
Why is it that I have to figure things out and explain them to you? What do you do?
- 我不拐彎抹角，而且我說到做到 - 真令人敬佩
- I say what I mean, and I do what I say. - Mm, how admirable.
- 是的 - 除了和我們有關的事以外
- You bet. - Except none of it's about us.
不
No.
我也許沉溺於大麻和百憂解之中
I may be stoned on grass and Prozac...
但你在我們的生活中如同死了
...but you've been walking through our life dead.
我得自貶身價，找上雷夫 以便終斷我們的關係
Now I have to demean myself with Ralph just to get closure with you.
護照、旅行支票、信用卡
Passports, traveler's checks, plastic.
在洛杉磯機場包機站十七號機庫
The plane, charter terminal, LAX, Hangar 17.
呼叫信號是1011S
Call letters are 1011 Sierra.
飛機會降落，等你五分鐘後便會起飛
Touches down, holds for you five minutes, then splits.
飛機會通過航空局檢查等手續
The plane will stand an FAA check. Filed a flight plan, the works.
- 克裏斯呢？ - 他走了
- Hey, where's Chris? - He's gone.
什麼？
What?
他說他要去找夏琳
Said he's going on his own. Went to look for Charlene.
- 你不是把他帶來了這裏了？ - 我有
- Didn't you bring him here? - Yeah, I brought him here.
怎麼回事？
What happened?
這是個自由國家
It's a free country, brother.
晚上九點聯絡我，確保一切妥當
Check in with me at 9. Everything's still cool.
好
All right.
我已經不知道自己在做什麼
I don't even know what I'm doing anymore.
我知道人生苦短
I know life is short.
能活多久是運氣
Whatever time you get is luck.
你想離開？
You wanna walk?
你現在就離開
You walk right now.
不然就你自願···
Or on your own...
你選擇自願跟我走
On your own, you choose to come with me.
我只知道
All I know is...
到任何地方去對我都無所謂
All I know is there's no point in me going anywhere anymore...
如果我得獨自一人
...if it's gonna be alone...
沒有你在身邊
...without you.
伊迪
Eady.
- 是 - 文森，我們準備行動
- Yeah. - Yeah, Vincent, I got a live one.
好，我等
Okay, I'll hold.
親愛的，讓克裏斯看見你吧
Come on, sugar. Show yourself.
- 是啊，快去做 - 住口！
- Yeah, do it. - Shut up!
只需要在窗前站一秒
Now, just one second at the window...
此事就會了結
...and it's all over.
夥計
Hey, man.
- 是？ - 你知道···
- Yeah? - You know any, uh...
這附近有地方出租嗎？
...place to rent around here?
有
Yeah.
載爾大道上的亞伯理茲雜貨店 牆上有招租告示
Alberiz's Grocer on Dell Avenue got cards on the wall.
好，謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
不是他，不是克裏斯
It's not him. It's not Chris.
第二小組，這是指揮部
Unit 2, this is Command.
攔阻他並查看身份
Take him at the street and check him out.
收到
10-4.
- 警官？ - 是
- Sergeant? - Yeah.
這人叫約翰彼得森，駕照有效
This guy's John Peterson. Valid ID.
車輛登記人是金布考斯基
Car's registered to the last name Bukowski, first name Gene.
向監理所查過，沒有不妥
Ran it to DMV. It's clean.
- 讓他走 - 知道
- Let him go. - Roger.
非常謝謝，晚安
Thank you very much. Have a good evening.
不是他，文森
It's a no-go, Vince.
薛哈利斯太太，我們在等的時候 要喝杯咖啡嗎？
Would you like a cup of coffee while we wait, Mrs. Shiherlis?
可以的話就太好了
Yeah, that'd be nice.
- 是？ - 有什麼消息？
- Yeah? - Yeah, what do you got?
沒事發生
Nothing's happening.
- 是？ - 是文森
- Yeah? - Hello, it's Vincent.
有何動靜？
What do you got?
沒有，韋恩葛羅去拿冰塊，就這樣
Nothing's going on. Waingro went for ice. That's it.
你知道嗎？
You know what?
尼爾走了
Neil is gone.
磅
Bam!
- 像鳥兒般飛走 - 文森，你怎麼知道？
- Flying like a bird. - Come on, Vincent, how do you know?
- 我們仍有誘餌，也許還有時間！ - 有，我們有什麼？
- We still got bait. Maybe some time! - Got, got. What do we got?
我們有什麼？
What do we got?
旅途愉快，雜種
Bon voyage, motherfucker.
你很行
You were good.
我要去住旅館
I'm going to the hotel.
我要去洗澡
I'm gonna take a shower.
睡一個月的覺
Gonna sleep for a month.
用這個
Over here.
寶貝，快醒來
Come on, baby.
好，好
Okay, okay.
該死
Shit.
讓我綁緊
Let me tighten this.
這樣浪費生命
What a fucking waste.
好，這裏
Okay, here.
渾蛋經常自毀，你不會死的 寶貝，你不會的
Assholes shoot themselves all fucking day. Not you, baby. Not you.
她會在哪裏？她叫蘿倫 蘿倫古絲塔芙森
Where would she be? Her name is Lauren, Lauren Gustafson.
她應該在這裏，但警方告訴我···
I'm supposed to be here with her. But the police...
- 我需要人幫忙··· - 沒關係，我可以
- Help me. I need somebody to help... - It's okay.
我抱著你
I got you.
我抱著你，寶貝
I got you, baby.
你會沒事的，親愛的 會沒事的，我保證
It'll be all right, honey. I swear. It's okay, baby.
找醫生來！我要醫生！你媽媽在這
Let's get a doctor! Let's go! A doctor here! There's your mama.
- 冷靜下來 - 你媽媽在這
- Let's just calm down. - Your mama's here.
- 她有服用藥物嗎？ - 沒有
- Is she on any drugs? - No.
找創傷及血管外科醫生來
I want you to get a trauma surgeon and a vascular surgeon.
她好像割斷了兩條動脈，幾乎沒有脈搏
I think she cut both arteries. Also, I could hardly feel her pulse.
她的血壓和呼吸下降，要給她插管
Her pressure's down. So is her respiration. You have to intubate her.
準備好了
It's ready.
- 最後一次任何人見到她是何時？ - 我不知道
- When's the last time anybody saw her? - I don't know.
- 你在哪裏找到她的？ - 浴缸
- Where did you find her? - The bathtub.
叫呼吸科，給她注射大針管的鹽水
Call Respiratory stat. Give her large-bore normal saline. Wide open.
持續對出血的血管施壓 需要兩公升O型血
Let's keep pressure on those bleeders. I need two units, O-negative.
- 查出她血型和再輸六公升 - 似乎有竇性心搏過速
- Let's type and cross her for six. - Looks like she's in sinus tach.
呼吸專家呢？我們需要幫忙
Where is Respiratory? We need more help.
快叫呼吸科醫生過來
Can you have Respiratory come now?
準備插管後照胸腔X光
Let's have x-ray ready for post-intubation chest x-ray.
令嬡己完成手術，現在在恢復室
Hi. Your daughter's out of surgery and she's in the recovery room now, okay?
她情況穩定 醫生很快會出來跟你們解釋
Her vital signs are stable. The surgeon will be out to speak to you in a few moments.
- 她沒事吧？ - 她很好
- She's okay? - She's doing good.
- 她會沒事的 - 她會沒事的
- She's gonna be okay. - She's gonna be okay.
- 她不會有事 - 我的寶貝
- Oh, my baby. - She's gonna be okay. It's all right.
- 沒事了 - 她為何這樣對自己？
- It's all right. - Why'd she do this to herself? Why?
看她把自己怎麼了
Look what she did. Look what she did to herself.
別難過
There.
沒事的，不會有事的
It's all right, honey. It's gonna be all right.
我在這裏，我哪裏也不去
I'm here. I ain't going anywhere.
- 明白嗎？ - 好
- You understand? - Yeah.
我哪裏也不去
I ain't going anywhere.
是？
Yeah?
是我
It's me.
飛機己在半空，會準時抵達
Plane's in the air now. It'll be right on time.
仍找不到可信任的司機
On the driver's end, I still can't find nobody, so that's in the trust.
還有一事
One other thing.
你既然問了，我就告訴你
You asked, so I gotta tell you.
你要找的人在馬奎斯酒店 化名「詹姆森」
The guy you wanted checked into the Marquis under "Jameson"...
如果你還在乎他的話 我猜你不會想找他
...if you still give a shit, which I figured you wouldn't.
- 你說得對 - 再見，兄弟
- You figured right. - So, so long, brother.
保重了
You take it easy.
你就要到終點了
You're home free.
保重
Take it easy.
- 怎麼了？ - 沒什麼
- What is it? - Nothing.
終點
Home free.
- 我得解決一些事情 - 有時間嗎？
- I gotta take care of something. - Is there time?
有的
There's time.
我很快回來，車子不要熄火
I'll be right back. Just leave her running.
- 入住登記 - 是，這是客房服務
- Registration. - Yeah, this is Room Service.
一個叫詹姆森的點了培根生菜三明治 但房號弄錯了，可以告訴我嗎？
A Jameson ordered a BLT. They screwed up his room number. Could you give it to me?
- 他們經常弄錯 - 是，我知道
- They're always doing that. - Yeah, I know.
- 是1735號房 - 謝謝
- 1735. - Thank you.
請注意
Your attention, please.
我們現在有火災警報
We are currently experiencing a fire alarm.
請不要驚慌，請不要乘坐電梯
Please do not panic. Please do not take the elevators.
- 該死 - 韋恩葛羅沒有動靜，我留在這
- Shit. - Waingro's not moving. I'm staying here.
我去查看樓梯，如果有煙，會叫你離開
I'm checking the stairs. If there's smoke, I'm pulling you out.
她父親呢？要我通知她父親嗎？
What about her dad? You want me to call him?
他在內華達山某處
He's somewhere in the Sierras.
而且她選了你
And she chose you.
選在你的房間自殺
She picked your place.
這種事不應該發生在她身上
It's not right, what happened to her.
是的，不應該
No, it's not.
是的
Ugh, okay.
有沒有辦法···
Is there any way...
能克服我們之間的問題？
...that it could work out between us?
我希望能說有
I wish I could say yes, you know.
可是終究···
But in the end...
像你說的
You know, it's like you said:
我一生全奉獻給被我追捕的罪犯
All I am, is what I'm going after.
我不是你想要的人，賈絲汀
I'm not what you want, Justine.
如果你需要走就走吧
Well, go on, if you have to.
不
No.
- 我可以留下來 - 我沒事，我可以應付
- I'll stay. - No, I'm okay. I can... I can handle this.
你自己小心
Just be careful.
打電話到這裏給我，讓我知道你沒事
Call me here. Let me know you're okay.
好嗎？
Okay?
走樓梯
Take the stairs.
誰？
Yeah?
酒店保全，三樓發生火警 各樓層的人都得疏散
Security. There's a fire on 3. We have to evacuate all the floors.
我不能離開
I can't leave here.
我們何不先談一下？
Why don't we just talk about this a bit, huh, brother?
他在17樓
He's here on 17.
看著我，看著我
Look at me. Look at me.
看著我
Look at me.
洛城警察，別動！手放在頭上！
L.A.P.D. Don't move. Put your hands on your head, now.
將我換到五號頻道
Switch me to TAC 5.
卡薩爾？ J J ？
Casals? JJ?
卓克，J J ？
Drucker, JJ?
文森，我在大廳的樓梯旁
I'm at the lobby level by the stairwell.
有什麼消息？
What have you got?
小組得乘坐其他的電梯去17樓
Teams are moving up the other elevators to the 17th floor elevators.
因為火警，電梯不能使用
All out of commission because of the fire alarm.
- 現場一團混亂 - 好，收到
- It's a mess. People everywhere. - Fine. 10-4.
趕快離開
Let's go, get out of the way.
不要擋路
Stay out of the way.
快，走那邊，好嗎？快點
Let's go. Go that way. We gotta go, all right? Go, go.
我知道了，長官
I got it, sir.
快點，快點
Come on, come on.
快走，先生
Come on, sir.
- 小心後面，女士們 - 我知道了
- Watch your backs, ladies. - I got it, I got it.
繼續走，夫人
Keep moving, ma'am.
走
Let's go.
繼續走
Come on, let's go.
走這邊，夫人
This way, ma'am.
後退，後退
Get back, get back.
- 把散彈鎗給我 - 是的，長官
- Let me have that shotgun. - Yes, sir.
我告訴過你，我不會回去坐牢的
Told you I'm never going back.
沒錯
Yeah.
譯者：James Liao